export const vowels = [
  {
    question: "What is this letter?",
    phonetic: "අ",
    correctAnswer: "a",
    answers: [
      { buttonLabel: "a", value: "a" },
      { buttonLabel: "e", value: "e" },
      { buttonLabel: "i", value: "i" },
      { buttonLabel: "u", value: "u" },
    ],
  },
  {
    question: "What is this letter?",
    phonetic: "ආ",
    correctAnswer: "ā",
    answers: [
      { buttonLabel: "ā", value: "ā" },
      { buttonLabel: "ē", value: "ē" },
      { buttonLabel: "ī", value: "ī" },
      { buttonLabel: "ū", value: "ū" },
    ],
  },
  {
    question: "What is this letter?",
    phonetic: "ා ",
    correctAnswer: "ā",
    answers: [
      { buttonLabel: "ā", value: "ā" },
      { buttonLabel: "ē", value: "ē" },
      { buttonLabel: "ī", value: "ī" },
      { buttonLabel: "ū", value: "ū" },
    ],
  },
  {
    question: "What is this letter?",
    phonetic: "ඇ",
    correctAnswer: "æ",
    answers: [
      { buttonLabel: "æ", value: "æ" },
      { buttonLabel: "ē", value: "ē" },
      { buttonLabel: "ī", value: "ī" },
      { buttonLabel: "ai", value: "ai" },
    ],
  },
  {
    question: "What is this letter?",
    phonetic: "ැ",
    correctAnswer: "æ",
    answers: [
      { buttonLabel: "æ", value: "æ" },
      { buttonLabel: "ē", value: "ē" },
      { buttonLabel: "ī", value: "ī" },
      { buttonLabel: "ai", value: "ai" },
    ],
  },
  {
    question: "What is this letter?",
    phonetic: "ඈ",
    correctAnswer: "ǣ",
    answers: [
      { buttonLabel: "ǣ", value: "ǣ" },
      { buttonLabel: "ē", value: "ē" },
      { buttonLabel: "ū", value: "ū" },
      { buttonLabel: "ai", value: "ai" },
    ],
  },
  {
    question: "What is this letter?",
    phonetic: "ෑ",
    correctAnswer: "ǣ",
    answers: [
      { buttonLabel: "ǣ", value: "ǣ" },
      { buttonLabel: "ē", value: "ē" },
      { buttonLabel: "ū", value: "ū" },
      { buttonLabel: "ai", value: "ai" },
    ],
  },
  {
    question: "What is this letter?",
    phonetic: "ඓ",
    correctAnswer: "ai",
    answers: [
      { buttonLabel: "ai", value: "ai" },
      { buttonLabel: "ē", value: "ē" },
      { buttonLabel: "ū", value: "ū" },
      { buttonLabel: "ǣ", value: "ǣ" },
    ],
  },
  {
    question: "What is this letter?",
    phonetic: "ෛ",
    correctAnswer: "ai",
    answers: [
      { buttonLabel: "ai", value: "ai" },
      { buttonLabel: "ē", value: "ē" },
      { buttonLabel: "ū", value: "ū" },
      { buttonLabel: "ǣ", value: "ǣ" },
    ],
  },
  {
    question: "What is this letter?",
    phonetic: "ඖ",
    correctAnswer: "au",
    answers: [
      { buttonLabel: "au", value: "au" },
      { buttonLabel: "ai", value: "ai" },
      { buttonLabel: "ū", value: "ū" },
      { buttonLabel: "ǣ", value: "ǣ" },
    ],
  },
  {
    question: "What is this letter?",
    phonetic: "ෞ",
    correctAnswer: "au",
    answers: [
      { buttonLabel: "au", value: "au" },
      { buttonLabel: "ai", value: "ai" },
      { buttonLabel: "ū", value: "ū" },
      { buttonLabel: "ǣ", value: "ǣ" },
    ],
  },
  {
    question: "What is this letter?",
    phonetic: "එ",
    correctAnswer: "e",
    answers: [
      { buttonLabel: "a", value: "a" },
      { buttonLabel: "e", value: "e" },
      { buttonLabel: "i", value: "i" },
      { buttonLabel: "u", value: "u" },
    ],
  },
  {
    question: "What is this letter?",
    phonetic: "ෙ",
    correctAnswer: "e",
    answers: [
      { buttonLabel: "a", value: "a" },
      { buttonLabel: "e", value: "e" },
      { buttonLabel: "i", value: "i" },
      { buttonLabel: "u", value: "u" },
    ],
  },
  {
    question: "What is this letter?",
    phonetic: "ඒ",
    correctAnswer: "ē",
    answers: [
      { buttonLabel: "ā", value: "ā" },
      { buttonLabel: "ē", value: "ē" },
      { buttonLabel: "ī", value: "ī" },
      { buttonLabel: "ū", value: "ū" },
    ],
  },
  {
    question: "What is this letter?",
    phonetic: "ේ",
    correctAnswer: "ē",
    answers: [
      { buttonLabel: "ā", value: "ā" },
      { buttonLabel: "ē", value: "ē" },
      { buttonLabel: "ī", value: "ī" },
      { buttonLabel: "ū", value: "ū" },
    ],
  },
  {
    question: "What is this letter?",
    phonetic: "ඉ",
    correctAnswer: "i",
    answers: [
      { buttonLabel: "a", value: "a" },
      { buttonLabel: "e", value: "e" },
      { buttonLabel: "i", value: "i" },
      { buttonLabel: "u", value: "u" },
    ],
  },
  {
    question: "What is this letter?",
    phonetic: "ි",
    correctAnswer: "i",
    answers: [
      { buttonLabel: "a", value: "a" },
      { buttonLabel: "e", value: "e" },
      { buttonLabel: "i", value: "i" },
      { buttonLabel: "u", value: "u" },
    ],
  },
  {
    question: "What is this letter?",
    phonetic: "ඊ",
    correctAnswer: "ī",
    answers: [
      { buttonLabel: "ā", value: "ā" },
      { buttonLabel: "ē", value: "ē" },
      { buttonLabel: "ī", value: "ī" },
      { buttonLabel: "ū", value: "ū" },
    ],
  },
  {
    question: "What is this letter?",
    phonetic: "ී",
    correctAnswer: "ī",
    answers: [
      { buttonLabel: "ā", value: "ā" },
      { buttonLabel: "ē", value: "ē" },
      { buttonLabel: "ī", value: "ī" },
      { buttonLabel: "ū", value: "ū" },
    ],
  },
  {
    question: "What is this letter?",
    phonetic: "ඔ",
    correctAnswer: "o",
    answers: [
      { buttonLabel: "a", value: "a" },
      { buttonLabel: "e", value: "e" },
      { buttonLabel: "o", value: "o" },
      { buttonLabel: "u", value: "u" },
    ],
  },
  {
    question: "What is this letter?",
    phonetic: "ො",
    correctAnswer: "o",
    answers: [
      { buttonLabel: "a", value: "a" },
      { buttonLabel: "e", value: "e" },
      { buttonLabel: "o", value: "o" },
      { buttonLabel: "u", value: "u" },
    ],
  },
  {
    question: "What is this letter?",
    phonetic: "ඕ",
    correctAnswer: "ō",
    answers: [
      { buttonLabel: "ā", value: "ā" },
      { buttonLabel: "ē", value: "ē" },
      { buttonLabel: "ō", value: "ō" },
      { buttonLabel: "ū", value: "ū" },
    ],
  },
  {
    question: "What is this letter?",
    phonetic: "ෝ",
    correctAnswer: "ō",
    answers: [
      { buttonLabel: "ā", value: "ā" },
      { buttonLabel: "ē", value: "ē" },
      { buttonLabel: "ō", value: "ō" },
      { buttonLabel: "ū", value: "ū" },
    ],
  },
  {
    question: "What is this letter?",
    phonetic: "උ",
    correctAnswer: "u",
    answers: [
      { buttonLabel: "a", value: "a" },
      { buttonLabel: "e", value: "e" },
      { buttonLabel: "o", value: "o" },
      { buttonLabel: "u", value: "u" },
    ],
  },
  {
    question: "What is this letter?",
    phonetic: "ු",
    correctAnswer: "u",
    answers: [
      { buttonLabel: "a", value: "a" },
      { buttonLabel: "e", value: "e" },
      { buttonLabel: "o", value: "o" },
      { buttonLabel: "u", value: "u" },
    ],
  },
  {
    question: "What is this letter?",
    phonetic: "ඌ",
    correctAnswer: "ū",
    answers: [
      { buttonLabel: "ā", value: "ā" },
      { buttonLabel: "ē", value: "ē" },
      { buttonLabel: "ō", value: "ō" },
      { buttonLabel: "ū", value: "ū" },
    ],
  },
  {
    question: "What is this letter?",
    phonetic: "ූ",
    correctAnswer: "ū",
    answers: [
      { buttonLabel: "ā", value: "ā" },
      { buttonLabel: "ē", value: "ē" },
      { buttonLabel: "ō", value: "ō" },
      { buttonLabel: "ū", value: "ū" },
    ],
  },
];

export const consonants = [
  {
    question: "What is this letter?",
    phonetic: "ක",
    correctAnswer: "ka",
    answers: [
      { buttonLabel: "ka", value: "ka" },
      { buttonLabel: "kha", value: "kha" },
      { buttonLabel: "ga", value: "ga" },
      { buttonLabel: "gha", value: "gha" },
    ],
  },
  {
    question: "What is this letter?",
    phonetic: "ඛ",
    correctAnswer: "kha",
    answers: [
      { buttonLabel: "ka", value: "ka" },
      { buttonLabel: "kha", value: "kha" },
      { buttonLabel: "ga", value: "ga" },
      { buttonLabel: "gha", value: "gha" },
    ],
  },
  {
    question: "What is this letter?",
    phonetic: "ග",
    correctAnswer: "ga",
    answers: [
      { buttonLabel: "ga", value: "ga" },
      { buttonLabel: "gha", value: "gha" },
      { buttonLabel: "ka", value: "ka" },
      { buttonLabel: "kha", value: "kha" },
    ],
  },
  {
    question: "What is this letter?",
    phonetic: "ඝ",
    correctAnswer: "gha",
    answers: [
      { buttonLabel: "gha", value: "gha" },
      { buttonLabel: "ga", value: "ga" },
      { buttonLabel: "kha", value: "kha" },
      { buttonLabel: "ka", value: "ka" },
    ],
  },
  {
    question: "What is this letter?",
    phonetic: "ඞ",
    correctAnswer: "nga",
    answers: [
      { buttonLabel: "nga", value: "nga" },
      { buttonLabel: "ṅga", value: "ṅga" },
      { buttonLabel: "ñga", value: "ñga" },
      { buttonLabel: "ga", value: "ga" },
    ],
  },
  {
    question: "What is this letter?",
    phonetic: "ඟ",
    correctAnswer: "ṅga",
    answers: [
      { buttonLabel: "ṅga", value: "ṅga" },
      { buttonLabel: "nga", value: "nga" },
      { buttonLabel: "ñga", value: "ñga" },
      { buttonLabel: "ga", value: "ga" },
    ],
  },
  {
    question: "What is this letter?",
    phonetic: "ච",
    correctAnswer: "ca",
    answers: [
      { buttonLabel: "ca", value: "ca" },
      { buttonLabel: "cha", value: "cha" },
      { buttonLabel: "ja", value: "ja" },
      { buttonLabel: "jha", value: "jha" },
    ],
  },
  {
    question: "What is this letter?",
    phonetic: "ඡ",
    correctAnswer: "cha",
    answers: [
      { buttonLabel: "cha", value: "cha" },
      { buttonLabel: "ca", value: "ca" },
      { buttonLabel: "ja", value: "ja" },
      { buttonLabel: "jha", value: "jha" },
    ],
  },
  {
    question: "What is this letter?",
    phonetic: "ජ",
    correctAnswer: "ja",
    answers: [
      { buttonLabel: "ja", value: "ja" },
      { buttonLabel: "jha", value: "jha" },
      { buttonLabel: "ca", value: "ca" },
      { buttonLabel: "cha", value: "cha" },
    ],
  },
  {
    question: "What is this letter?",
    phonetic: "ඣ",
    correctAnswer: "jha",
    answers: [
      { buttonLabel: "jha", value: "jha" },
      { buttonLabel: "ja", value: "ja" },
      { buttonLabel: "cha", value: "cha" },
      { buttonLabel: "ca", value: "ca" },
    ],
  },
  {
    question: "What is this letter?",
    phonetic: "ඤ",
    correctAnswer: "ñya",
    answers: [
      { buttonLabel: "ñya", value: "ñya" },
      { buttonLabel: "jñya", value: "jñya" },
      { buttonLabel: "ñja", value: "ñja" },
      { buttonLabel: "jha", value: "jha" },
    ],
  },
  {
    question: "What is this letter?",
    phonetic: "ඥ",
    correctAnswer: "jñya",
    answers: [
      { buttonLabel: "jñya", value: "jñya" },
      { buttonLabel: "ñya", value: "ñya" },
      { buttonLabel: "ñja", value: "ñja" },
      { buttonLabel: "ja", value: "ja" },
    ],
  },
  {
    question: "What is this letter?",
    phonetic: "ඦ",
    correctAnswer: "ñja",
    answers: [
      { buttonLabel: "ñja", value: "ñja" },
      { buttonLabel: "jñya", value: "jñya" },
      { buttonLabel: "ñya", value: "ñya" },
      { buttonLabel: "ja", value: "ja" },
    ],
  },
  {
    question: "What is this letter?",
    phonetic: "ට",
    correctAnswer: "ṭa",
    answers: [
      { buttonLabel: "ṭa", value: "ṭa" },
      { buttonLabel: "ṭha", value: "ṭha" },
      { buttonLabel: "ḍa", value: "ḍa" },
      { buttonLabel: "ḍha", value: "ḍha" },
    ],
  },
  {
    question: "What is this letter?",
    phonetic: "ඨ",
    correctAnswer: "ṭha",
    answers: [
      { buttonLabel: "ṭha", value: "ṭha" },
      { buttonLabel: "ṭa", value: "ṭa" },
      { buttonLabel: "ḍa", value: "ḍa" },
      { buttonLabel: "ḍha", value: "ḍha" },
    ],
  },
  {
    question: "What is this letter?",
    phonetic: "ඩ",
    correctAnswer: "ḍa",
    answers: [
      { buttonLabel: "ḍa", value: "ḍa" },
      { buttonLabel: "ḍha", value: "ḍha" },
      { buttonLabel: "ṭa", value: "ṭa" },
      { buttonLabel: "ṭha", value: "ṭha" },
    ],
  },
  {
    question: "What is this letter?",
    phonetic: "ඪ",
    correctAnswer: "ḍha",
    answers: [
      { buttonLabel: "ḍha", value: "ḍha" },
      { buttonLabel: "ḍa", value: "ḍa" },
      { buttonLabel: "ṭa", value: "ṭa" },
      { buttonLabel: "ṭha", value: "ṭha" },
    ],
  },
  {
    question: "What is this letter?",
    phonetic: "ණ",
    correctAnswer: "ṇa",
    answers: [
      { buttonLabel: "ṇa", value: "ṇa" },
      { buttonLabel: "ṇḍa", value: "ṇḍa" },
      { buttonLabel: "ḍa", value: "ḍa" },
      { buttonLabel: "ḍha", value: "ḍha" },
    ],
  },
  {
    question: "What is this letter?",
    phonetic: "ඬ",
    correctAnswer: "ṇḍa",
    answers: [
      { buttonLabel: "ṇḍa", value: "ṇḍa" },
      { buttonLabel: "ṇa", value: "ṇa" },
      { buttonLabel: "ḍa", value: "ḍa" },
      { buttonLabel: "ḍha", value: "ḍha" },
    ],
  },
  {
    question: "What is this letter?",
    phonetic: "ත",
    correctAnswer: "ta",
    answers: [
      { buttonLabel: "ta", value: "ta" },
      { buttonLabel: "tha", value: "tha" },
      { buttonLabel: "da", value: "da" },
      { buttonLabel: "dha", value: "dha" },
    ],
  },
  {
    question: "What is this letter?",
    phonetic: "ථ",
    correctAnswer: "tha",
    answers: [
      { buttonLabel: "tha", value: "tha" },
      { buttonLabel: "ta", value: "ta" },
      { buttonLabel: "da", value: "da" },
      { buttonLabel: "dha", value: "dha" },
    ],
  },
  {
    question: "What is this letter?",
    phonetic: "ද",
    correctAnswer: "da",
    answers: [
      { buttonLabel: "da", value: "da" },
      { buttonLabel: "dha", value: "dha" },
      { buttonLabel: "ta", value: "ta" },
      { buttonLabel: "tha", value: "tha" },
    ],
  },
  {
    question: "What is this letter?",
    phonetic: "ධ",
    correctAnswer: "dha",
    answers: [
      { buttonLabel: "dha", value: "dha" },
      { buttonLabel: "da", value: "da" },
      { buttonLabel: "ta", value: "ta" },
      { buttonLabel: "tha", value: "tha" },
    ],
  },
  {
    question: "What is this letter?",
    phonetic: "න",
    correctAnswer: "na",
    answers: [
      { buttonLabel: "na", value: "na" },
      { buttonLabel: "nda", value: "nda" },
      { buttonLabel: "da", value: "da" },
      { buttonLabel: "dha", value: "dha" },
    ],
  },
  {
    question: "What is this letter?",
    phonetic: "ඳ",
    correctAnswer: "nda",
    answers: [
      { buttonLabel: "nda", value: "nda" },
      { buttonLabel: "na", value: "na" },
      { buttonLabel: "da", value: "da" },
      { buttonLabel: "dha", value: "dha" },
    ],
  },
  {
    question: "What is this letter?",
    phonetic: "ප",
    correctAnswer: "pa",
    answers: [
      { buttonLabel: "pa", value: "pa" },
      { buttonLabel: "pha", value: "pha" },
      { buttonLabel: "ba", value: "ba" },
      { buttonLabel: "bha", value: "bha" },
    ],
  },
  {
    question: "What is this letter?",
    phonetic: "ඵ",
    correctAnswer: "pha",
    answers: [
      { buttonLabel: "pha", value: "pha" },
      { buttonLabel: "pa", value: "pa" },
      { buttonLabel: "ba", value: "ba" },
      { buttonLabel: "bha", value: "bha" },
    ],
  },
  {
    question: "What is this letter?",
    phonetic: "බ",
    correctAnswer: "ba",
    answers: [
      { buttonLabel: "ba", value: "ba" },
      { buttonLabel: "bha", value: "bha" },
      { buttonLabel: "ca", value: "ca" },
      { buttonLabel: "cha", value: "cha" },
    ],
  },
  {
    question: "What is this letter?",
    phonetic: "භ",
    correctAnswer: "bha",
    answers: [
      { buttonLabel: "bha", value: "bha" },
      { buttonLabel: "ba", value: "ba" },
      { buttonLabel: "pa", value: "pa" },
      { buttonLabel: "pha", value: "pha" },
    ],
  },
  {
    question: "What is this letter?",
    phonetic: "ම",
    correctAnswer: "ma",
    answers: [
      { buttonLabel: "ma", value: "ma" },
      { buttonLabel: "mba", value: "mba" },
      { buttonLabel: "ba", value: "ba" },
      { buttonLabel: "bha", value: "bha" },
    ],
  },
  {
    question: "What is this letter?",
    phonetic: "ඹ",
    correctAnswer: "mba",
    answers: [
      { buttonLabel: "mba", value: "mba" },
      { buttonLabel: "ma", value: "ma" },
      { buttonLabel: "ba", value: "ba" },
      { buttonLabel: "bha", value: "bha" },
    ],
  },
  {
    question: "What is this letter?",
    phonetic: "ය",
    correctAnswer: "ya",
    answers: [
      { buttonLabel: "ya", value: "ya" },
      { buttonLabel: "ra", value: "ra" },
      { buttonLabel: "la", value: "la" },
      { buttonLabel: "va", value: "va" },
    ],
  },
  {
    question: "What is this letter?",
    phonetic: "ර",
    correctAnswer: "ra",
    answers: [
      { buttonLabel: "ra", value: "ra" },
      { buttonLabel: "ya", value: "ya" },
      { buttonLabel: "la", value: "la" },
      { buttonLabel: "va", value: "va" },
    ],
  },
  {
    question: "What is this letter?",
    phonetic: "ල",
    correctAnswer: "la",
    answers: [
      { buttonLabel: "la", value: "la" },
      { buttonLabel: "ya", value: "ya" },
      { buttonLabel: "ra", value: "ra" },
      { buttonLabel: "va", value: "va" },
    ],
  },
  {
    question: "What is this letter?",
    phonetic: "ව",
    correctAnswer: "va",
    answers: [
      { buttonLabel: "va", value: "va" },
      { buttonLabel: "la", value: "la" },
      { buttonLabel: "ra", value: "ra" },
      { buttonLabel: "ya", value: "ya" },
    ],
  },
  {
    question: "What is this letter?",
    phonetic: "ශ",
    correctAnswer: "śa",
    answers: [
      { buttonLabel: "śa", value: "śa" },
      { buttonLabel: "ṣa", value: "ṣa" },
      { buttonLabel: "sa", value: "sa" },
      { buttonLabel: "ha", value: "ha" },
    ],
  },
  {
    question: "What is this letter?",
    phonetic: "ෂ",
    correctAnswer: "ṣa",
    answers: [
      { buttonLabel: "ṣa", value: "ṣa" },
      { buttonLabel: "śa", value: "śa" },
      { buttonLabel: "sa", value: "sa" },
      { buttonLabel: "ha", value: "ha" },
    ],
  },
  {
    question: "What is this letter?",
    phonetic: "ක්‍ෂ",
    correctAnswer: "ṣa",
    answers: [
      { buttonLabel: "ṣa", value: "ṣa" },
      { buttonLabel: "śa", value: "śa" },
      { buttonLabel: "sa", value: "sa" },
      { buttonLabel: "ha", value: "ha" },
    ],
  },
  {
    question: "What is this letter?",
    phonetic: "ස",
    correctAnswer: "sa",
    answers: [
      { buttonLabel: "sa", value: "sa" },
      { buttonLabel: "śa", value: "śa" },
      { buttonLabel: "ṣa", value: "ṣa" },
      { buttonLabel: "ha", value: "ha" },
    ],
  },
  {
    question: "What is this letter?",
    phonetic: "හ",
    correctAnswer: "ha",
    answers: [
      { buttonLabel: "ha", value: "ha" },
      { buttonLabel: "sa", value: "sa" },
      { buttonLabel: "śa", value: "śa" },
      { buttonLabel: "ṣa", value: "ṣa" },
    ],
  },
  {
    question: "What is this letter?",
    phonetic: "ළ",
    correctAnswer: "ḷa",
    answers: [
      { buttonLabel: "ḷa", value: "ḷa" },
      { buttonLabel: "la", value: "la" },
      { buttonLabel: "ra", value: "ra" },
      { buttonLabel: "va", value: "va" },
    ],
  },
  {
    question: "What is this letter?",
    phonetic: "ෆ",
    correctAnswer: "fa",
    answers: [
      { buttonLabel: "fa", value: "fa" },
      { buttonLabel: "pha", value: "pha" },
      { buttonLabel: "pa", value: "pa" },
      { buttonLabel: "ba", value: "ba" },
    ],
  },
];

export const numbers = [
  [
    {
      question: "What is this number?",
      phonetic: "0",
      correctAnswer: "zero",
      answers: [
        { buttonLabel: "tuna", value: "three", sinhala: "තුන" },
        { buttonLabel: "deka", value: "two", sinhala: "දෙක" },
        { buttonLabel: "eka", value: "one", sinhala: "එක" },
        { buttonLabel: "binduva", value: "zero", sinhala: "බින්දුව" },
      ],
    },
    {
      question: "What is this number?",
      phonetic: "බින්දුව",
      correctAnswer: "0",
      answers: [
        { buttonLabel: "0", value: "0" },
        { buttonLabel: "1", value: "1" },
        { buttonLabel: "4", value: "4" },
        { buttonLabel: "7", value: "7" },
      ],
    },
    {
      question: "What is this number?",
      phonetic: "1",
      correctAnswer: "one",
      answers: [
        { buttonLabel: "tuna", value: "three", sinhala: "තුන" },
        { buttonLabel: "deka", value: "two", sinhala: "දෙක" },
        { buttonLabel: "eka", value: "one", sinhala: "එක" },
        { buttonLabel: "binduva", value: "zero", sinhala: "බින්දුව" },
      ],
    },
    {
      question: "What is this number?",
      phonetic: "එක",
      correctAnswer: "1",
      answers: [
        { buttonLabel: "0", value: "0" },
        { buttonLabel: "1", value: "1" },
        { buttonLabel: "4", value: "4" },
        { buttonLabel: "7", value: "7" },
      ],
    },
    {
      question: "What is this number?",
      phonetic: "2",
      correctAnswer: "two",
      answers: [
        { buttonLabel: "tuna", value: "three", sinhala: "තුන" },
        { buttonLabel: "deka", value: "two", sinhala: "දෙක" },
        { buttonLabel: "eka", value: "one", sinhala: "එක" },
        { buttonLabel: "binduva", value: "zero", sinhala: "බින්දුව" },
      ],
    },
    {
      question: "What is this number?",
      phonetic: "දෙක",
      correctAnswer: "2",
      answers: [
        { buttonLabel: "2", value: "2" },
        { buttonLabel: "3", value: "3" },
        { buttonLabel: "5", value: "5" },
        { buttonLabel: "8", value: "8" },
      ],
    },
    {
      question: "What is this number?",
      phonetic: "3",
      correctAnswer: "three",
      answers: [
        { buttonLabel: "tuna", value: "three", sinhala: "තුන" },
        { buttonLabel: "haya", value: "six", sinhala: "හ‍ය" },
        { buttonLabel: "paha", value: "five", sinhala: "පහ" },
        { buttonLabel: "hatara", value: "four", sinhala: "හතර" },
      ],
    },
    {
      question: "What is this number?",
      phonetic: "තුන",
      correctAnswer: "3",
      answers: [
        { buttonLabel: "2", value: "2" },
        { buttonLabel: "3", value: "3" },
        { buttonLabel: "5", value: "5" },
        { buttonLabel: "8", value: "8" },
      ],
    },
    {
      question: "What is this number?",
      phonetic: "4",
      correctAnswer: "four",
      answers: [
        { buttonLabel: "tuna", value: "three", sinhala: "තුන" },
        { buttonLabel: "haya", value: "six", sinhala: "හ‍ය" },
        { buttonLabel: "paha", value: "five", sinhala: "පහ" },
        { buttonLabel: "hatara", value: "four", sinhala: "හතර" },
      ],
    },
    {
      question: "What is this number?",
      phonetic: "හතර",
      correctAnswer: "4",
      answers: [
        { buttonLabel: "4", value: "4" },
        { buttonLabel: "3", value: "3" },
        { buttonLabel: "5", value: "5" },
        { buttonLabel: "8", value: "8" },
      ],
    },
    {
      question: "What is this number?",
      phonetic: "5",
      correctAnswer: "five",
      answers: [
        { buttonLabel: "tuna", value: "three", sinhala: "තුන" },
        { buttonLabel: "haya", value: "six", sinhala: "හ‍ය" },
        { buttonLabel: "paha", value: "five", sinhala: "පහ" },
        { buttonLabel: "hatara", value: "four", sinhala: "හතර" },
      ],
    },
    {
      question: "What is this number?",
      phonetic: "පහ",
      correctAnswer: "5",
      answers: [
        { buttonLabel: "9", value: "9" },
        { buttonLabel: "3", value: "3" },
        { buttonLabel: "5", value: "5" },
        { buttonLabel: "8", value: "8" },
      ],
    },
    {
      question: "What is this number?",
      phonetic: "6",
      correctAnswer: "six",
      answers: [
        { buttonLabel: "tuna", value: "three", sinhala: "තුන" },
        { buttonLabel: "haya", value: "six", sinhala: "හ‍ය" },
        { buttonLabel: "paha", value: "five", sinhala: "පහ" },
        { buttonLabel: "hatara", value: "four", sinhala: "හතර" },
      ],
    },
    {
      question: "What is this number?",
      phonetic: "හ‍ය",
      correctAnswer: "6",
      answers: [
        { buttonLabel: "9", value: "9" },
        { buttonLabel: "6", value: "6" },
        { buttonLabel: "5", value: "5" },
        { buttonLabel: "8", value: "8" },
      ],
    },
    {
      question: "What is this number?",
      phonetic: "7",
      correctAnswer: "seven",
      answers: [
        { buttonLabel: "namaya", value: "nine", sinhala: "නම‍ය" },
        { buttonLabel: "hata", value: "seven", sinhala: "හත" },
        { buttonLabel: "dahaya", value: "ten", sinhala: "දහ‍ය" },
        { buttonLabel: "aṭa", value: "eight", sinhala: "අට" },
      ],
    },
    {
      question: "What is this number?",
      phonetic: "හත",
      correctAnswer: "7",
      answers: [
        { buttonLabel: "9", value: "9" },
        { buttonLabel: "7", value: "7" },
        { buttonLabel: "5", value: "5" },
        { buttonLabel: "8", value: "8" },
      ],
    },
    {
      question: "What is this number?",
      phonetic: "8",
      correctAnswer: "eight",
      answers: [
        { buttonLabel: "namaya", value: "nine", sinhala: "නම‍ය" },
        { buttonLabel: "hata", value: "seven", sinhala: "හත" },
        { buttonLabel: "dahaya", value: "ten", sinhala: "දහ‍ය" },
        { buttonLabel: "aṭa", value: "eight", sinhala: "අට" },
      ],
    },
    {
      question: "What is this number?",
      phonetic: "අට",
      correctAnswer: "8",
      answers: [
        { buttonLabel: "9", value: "9" },
        { buttonLabel: "7", value: "7" },
        { buttonLabel: "5", value: "5" },
        { buttonLabel: "8", value: "8" },
      ],
    },
    {
      question: "What is this number?",
      phonetic: "9",
      correctAnswer: "nine",
      answers: [
        { buttonLabel: "namaya", value: "nine", sinhala: "නම‍ය" },
        { buttonLabel: "hata", value: "seven", sinhala: "හත" },
        { buttonLabel: "dahaya", value: "ten", sinhala: "දහ‍ය" },
        { buttonLabel: "aṭa", value: "eight", sinhala: "අට" },
      ],
    },
    {
      question: "What is this number?",
      phonetic: "නම‍ය",
      correctAnswer: "9",
      answers: [
        { buttonLabel: "9", value: "9" },
        { buttonLabel: "7", value: "7" },
        { buttonLabel: "10", value: "10" },
        { buttonLabel: "8", value: "8" },
      ],
    },
    {
      question: "What is this number?",
      phonetic: "10",
      correctAnswer: "ten",
      answers: [
        { buttonLabel: "namaya", value: "nine", sinhala: "නම‍ය" },
        { buttonLabel: "hata", value: "seven", sinhala: "හත" },
        { buttonLabel: "dahaya", value: "ten", sinhala: "දහ‍ය" },
        { buttonLabel: "aṭa", value: "eight", sinhala: "අට" },
      ],
    },
    {
      question: "What is this number?",
      phonetic: "දහ‍ය",
      correctAnswer: "10",
      answers: [
        { buttonLabel: "9", value: "9" },
        { buttonLabel: "7", value: "7" },
        { buttonLabel: "10", value: "10" },
        { buttonLabel: "8", value: "8" },
      ],
    },
  ],
  [
    {
      question: "What is this number?",
      phonetic: "10",
      correctAnswer: "ten",
      answers: [
        { buttonLabel: "namaya", value: "nine", sinhala: "නම‍ය" },
        { buttonLabel: "hata", value: "seven", sinhala: "හත" },
        { buttonLabel: "dahaya", value: "ten", sinhala: "දහ‍ය" },
        { buttonLabel: "aṭa", value: "eight", sinhala: "අට" },
      ],
    },
    {
      question: "What is this number?",
      phonetic: "දහ‍ය",
      correctAnswer: "10",
      answers: [
        { buttonLabel: "9", value: "9" },
        { buttonLabel: "7", value: "7" },
        { buttonLabel: "10", value: "10" },
        { buttonLabel: "8", value: "8" },
      ],
    },
    {
      question: "What is this number?",
      phonetic: "එකොළහ",
      correctAnswer: "11",
      answers: [
        { buttonLabel: "11", value: "11" },
        { buttonLabel: "15", value: "15" },
        { buttonLabel: "13", value: "13" },
        { buttonLabel: "16", value: "16" },
      ],
    },
    {
      question: "What is this number?",
      phonetic: "11",
      correctAnswer: "eleven",
      answers: [
        { buttonLabel: "ekoḷaha", value: "eleven", sinhala: "එකොළහ" },
        { buttonLabel: "pahaḷova", value: "fifteen", sinhala: "පහළොව" },
        { buttonLabel: "dahatuna", value: "thirteen", sinhala: "දහතුන" },
        { buttonLabel: "dāsaya", value: "sixteen", sinhala: "දාසය" },
      ],
    },
    {
      question: "What is this number?",
      phonetic: "දොළහ",
      correctAnswer: "12",
      answers: [
        { buttonLabel: "12", value: "12" },
        { buttonLabel: "18", value: "18" },
        { buttonLabel: "14", value: "14" },
        { buttonLabel: "20", value: "20" },
      ],
    },
    {
      question: "What is this number?",
      phonetic: "12",
      correctAnswer: "twelve",
      answers: [
        { buttonLabel: "doḷaha", value: "twelve", sinhala: "දොළහ" },
        { buttonLabel: "dahaaṭa", value: "eighteen", sinhala: "දහඅට" },
        { buttonLabel: "dāhatara", value: "fourteen", sinhala: "දාහතර" },
        { buttonLabel: "vissa", value: "twenty", sinhala: "විස්ස" },
      ],
    },
    {
      question: "What is this number?",
      phonetic: "දහතුන",
      correctAnswer: "13",
      answers: [
        { buttonLabel: "13", value: "13" },
        { buttonLabel: "17", value: "17" },
        { buttonLabel: "19", value: "19" },
        { buttonLabel: "11", value: "11" },
      ],
    },
    {
      question: "What is this number?",
      phonetic: "13",
      correctAnswer: "thirteen",
      answers: [
        { buttonLabel: "dahatuna", value: "thirteen", sinhala: "දහතුන" },
        { buttonLabel: "dāhata", value: "seventeen", sinhala: "දාහත" },
        { buttonLabel: "dahanamaya", value: "nineteen", sinhala: "දහනමය" },
        { buttonLabel: "ekoḷaha", value: "eleven", sinhala: "එකොළහ" },
      ],
    },
    {
      question: "What is this number?",
      phonetic: "දාහතර",
      correctAnswer: "14",
      answers: [
        { buttonLabel: "14", value: "14" },
        { buttonLabel: "20", value: "20" },
        { buttonLabel: "12", value: "12" },
        { buttonLabel: "16", value: "16" },
      ],
    },
    {
      question: "What is this number?",
      phonetic: "14",
      correctAnswer: "fourteen",
      answers: [
        { buttonLabel: "dāhatara", value: "fourteen", sinhala: "දාහතර" },
        { buttonLabel: "vissa", value: "twenty", sinhala: "විස්ස" },
        { buttonLabel: "doḷaha", value: "twelve", sinhala: "දොළහ" },
        { buttonLabel: "dāsaya", value: "sixteen", sinhala: "දාසය" },
      ],
    },
    {
      question: "What is this number?",
      phonetic: "පහළොව",
      correctAnswer: "15",
      answers: [
        { buttonLabel: "15", value: "15" },
        { buttonLabel: "19", value: "19" },
        { buttonLabel: "13", value: "13" },
        { buttonLabel: "17", value: "17" },
      ],
    },
    {
      question: "What is this number?",
      phonetic: "15",
      correctAnswer: "fifteen",
      answers: [
        { buttonLabel: "pahaḷova", value: "fifteen", sinhala: "පහළොව" },
        { buttonLabel: "dahanamaya", value: "nineteen", sinhala: "දහනමය" },
        { buttonLabel: "dahatuna", value: "thirteen", sinhala: "දහතුන" },
        { buttonLabel: "dāhata", value: "seventeen", sinhala: "දාහත" },
      ],
    },
    {
      question: "What is this number?",
      phonetic: "දාසය",
      correctAnswer: "16",
      answers: [
        { buttonLabel: "16", value: "16" },
        { buttonLabel: "18", value: "18" },
        { buttonLabel: "12", value: "12" },
        { buttonLabel: "14", value: "14" },
      ],
    },
    {
      question: "What is this number?",
      phonetic: "16",
      correctAnswer: "sixteen",
      answers: [
        { buttonLabel: "dāsaya", value: "sixteen", sinhala: "දාසය" },
        { buttonLabel: "dahaaṭa", value: "eighteen", sinhala: "දහඅට" },
        { buttonLabel: "doḷaha", value: "twelve", sinhala: "දොළහ" },
        { buttonLabel: "dāhatara", value: "fourteen", sinhala: "දාහතර" },
      ],
    },
    {
      question: "What is this number?",
      phonetic: "දාහත",
      correctAnswer: "17",
      answers: [
        { buttonLabel: "17", value: "17" },
        { buttonLabel: "15", value: "15" },
        { buttonLabel: "19", value: "19" },
        { buttonLabel: "13", value: "13" },
      ],
    },
    {
      question: "What is this number?",
      phonetic: "17",
      correctAnswer: "seventeen",
      answers: [
        { buttonLabel: "dāhata", value: "seventeen", sinhala: "දාහත" },
        { buttonLabel: "pahaḷova", value: "fifteen", sinhala: "පහළොව" },
        { buttonLabel: "dahanamaya", value: "nineteen", sinhala: "දහනමය" },
        { buttonLabel: "dahatuna", value: "thirteen", sinhala: "දහතුන" },
      ],
    },
    {
      question: "What is this number?",
      phonetic: "දහඅට",
      correctAnswer: "18",
      answers: [
        { buttonLabel: "18", value: "18" },
        { buttonLabel: "14", value: "14" },
        { buttonLabel: "12", value: "12" },
        { buttonLabel: "16", value: "16" },
      ],
    },
    {
      question: "What is this number?",
      phonetic: "18",
      correctAnswer: "eighteen",
      answers: [
        { buttonLabel: "dahaaṭa", value: "eighteen", sinhala: "දහඅට" },
        { buttonLabel: "dāhatara", value: "fourteen", sinhala: "දාහතර" },
        { buttonLabel: "doḷaha", value: "twelve", sinhala: "දොළහ" },
        { buttonLabel: "dāsaya", value: "sixteen", sinhala: "දාසය" },
      ],
    },
    {
      question: "What is this number?",
      phonetic: "දහනමය",
      correctAnswer: "19",
      answers: [
        { buttonLabel: "19", value: "19" },
        { buttonLabel: "17", value: "17" },
        { buttonLabel: "15", value: "15" },
        { buttonLabel: "13", value: "13" },
      ],
    },
    {
      question: "What is this number?",
      phonetic: "19",
      correctAnswer: "nineteen",
      answers: [
        { buttonLabel: "dahanamaya", value: "nineteen", sinhala: "දහනමය" },
        { buttonLabel: "dāhata", value: "seventeen", sinhala: "දාහත" },
        { buttonLabel: "pahaḷova", value: "fifteen", sinhala: "පහළොව" },
        { buttonLabel: "dahatuna", value: "thirteen", sinhala: "දහතුන" },
      ],
    },
    {
      question: "What is this number?",
      phonetic: "විස්ස",
      correctAnswer: "20",
      answers: [
        { buttonLabel: "20", value: "20" },
        { buttonLabel: "12", value: "12" },
        { buttonLabel: "18", value: "18" },
        { buttonLabel: "16", value: "16" },
      ],
    },
    {
      question: "What is this number?",
      phonetic: "20",
      correctAnswer: "twenty",
      answers: [
        { buttonLabel: "vissa", value: "twenty", sinhala: "විස්ස" },
        { buttonLabel: "doḷaha", value: "twelve", sinhala: "දොළහ" },
        { buttonLabel: "dahaaṭa", value: "eighteen", sinhala: "දහඅට" },
        { buttonLabel: "dāsaya", value: "sixteen", sinhala: "දාසය" },
      ],
    },
  ],
  [
    {
      question: "What is this number?",
      phonetic: "විස්ස",
      correctAnswer: "20",
      answers: [
        { buttonLabel: "20", value: "20" },
        { buttonLabel: "12", value: "12" },
        { buttonLabel: "18", value: "18" },
        { buttonLabel: "16", value: "16" },
      ],
    },
    {
      question: "What is this number?",
      phonetic: "20",
      correctAnswer: "twenty",
      answers: [
        { buttonLabel: "vissa", value: "twenty", sinhala: "විස්ස" },
        { buttonLabel: "doḷaha", value: "twelve", sinhala: "දොළහ" },
        { buttonLabel: "dahaaṭa", value: "eighteen", sinhala: "දහඅට" },
        { buttonLabel: "dāsaya", value: "sixteen", sinhala: "දාසය" },
      ],
    },
    {
      question: "What is this number?",
      phonetic: "විසි එක",
      correctAnswer: "21",
      answers: [
        { buttonLabel: "21", value: "21" },
        { buttonLabel: "25", value: "25" },
        { buttonLabel: "23", value: "23" },
        { buttonLabel: "26", value: "26" },
      ],
    },
    {
      question: "What is this number?",
      phonetic: "21",
      correctAnswer: "twenty-one",
      answers: [
        { buttonLabel: "visi eka", value: "twenty-one", sinhala: "විසි එක" },
        { buttonLabel: "visi paha", value: "twenty-five", sinhala: "විසි පහ" },
        {
          buttonLabel: "visi tuna",
          value: "twenty-three",
          sinhala: "විසි තුන",
        },
        { buttonLabel: "visi haya", value: "twenty-six", sinhala: "විසි හය" },
      ],
    },
    {
      question: "What is this number?",
      phonetic: "විසි දෙක",
      correctAnswer: "22",
      answers: [
        { buttonLabel: "22", value: "22" },
        { buttonLabel: "28", value: "28" },
        { buttonLabel: "24", value: "24" },
        { buttonLabel: "30", value: "30" },
      ],
    },
    {
      question: "What is this number?",
      phonetic: "22",
      correctAnswer: "twenty-two",
      answers: [
        { buttonLabel: "visi deka", value: "twenty-two", sinhala: "විසි දෙක" },
        { buttonLabel: "visi aṭa", value: "twenty-eight", sinhala: "විසි අට" },
        {
          buttonLabel: "visi hatara",
          value: "twenty-four",
          sinhala: "විසි හතර",
        },
        { buttonLabel: "tiha", value: "thirty", sinhala: "තිහ" },
      ],
    },
    {
      question: "What is this number?",
      phonetic: "විසි තුන",
      correctAnswer: "23",
      answers: [
        { buttonLabel: "23", value: "23" },
        { buttonLabel: "27", value: "27" },
        { buttonLabel: "29", value: "29" },
        { buttonLabel: "21", value: "21" },
      ],
    },
    {
      question: "What is this number?",
      phonetic: "23",
      correctAnswer: "twenty-three",
      answers: [
        {
          buttonLabel: "visi tuna",
          value: "twenty-three",
          sinhala: "විසි තුන",
        },
        { buttonLabel: "visi hata", value: "twenty-seven", sinhala: "විසි හත" },
        {
          buttonLabel: "visi namaya",
          value: "twenty-nine",
          sinhala: "විසි නමය",
        },
        { buttonLabel: "visi eka", value: "twenty-one", sinhala: "විසි එක" },
      ],
    },
    {
      question: "What is this number?",
      phonetic: "විසි හතර",
      correctAnswer: "24",
      answers: [
        { buttonLabel: "24", value: "24" },
        { buttonLabel: "30", value: "30" },
        { buttonLabel: "22", value: "22" },
        { buttonLabel: "26", value: "26" },
      ],
    },
    {
      question: "What is this number?",
      phonetic: "24",
      correctAnswer: "twenty-four",
      answers: [
        {
          buttonLabel: "visi hatara",
          value: "twenty-four",
          sinhala: "විසි හතර",
        },
        { buttonLabel: "tiha", value: "thirty", sinhala: "තිහ" },
        { buttonLabel: "visi deka", value: "twenty-two", sinhala: "විසි දෙක" },
        { buttonLabel: "visi haya", value: "twenty-six", sinhala: "විසි හය" },
      ],
    },
    {
      question: "What is this number?",
      phonetic: "විසි පහ",
      correctAnswer: "25",
      answers: [
        { buttonLabel: "25", value: "25" },
        { buttonLabel: "29", value: "29" },
        { buttonLabel: "23", value: "23" },
        { buttonLabel: "27", value: "27" },
      ],
    },
    {
      question: "What is this number?",
      phonetic: "25",
      correctAnswer: "twenty-five",
      answers: [
        { buttonLabel: "visi paha", value: "twenty-five", sinhala: "විසි පහ" },
        {
          buttonLabel: "visi namaya",
          value: "twenty-nine",
          sinhala: "විසි නමය",
        },
        {
          buttonLabel: "visi tuna",
          value: "twenty-three",
          sinhala: "විසි තුන",
        },
        { buttonLabel: "visi hata", value: "twenty-seven", sinhala: "විසි හත" },
      ],
    },
    {
      question: "What is this number?",
      phonetic: "විසි හය",
      correctAnswer: "26",
      answers: [
        { buttonLabel: "26", value: "26" },
        { buttonLabel: "28", value: "28" },
        { buttonLabel: "22", value: "22" },
        { buttonLabel: "24", value: "24" },
      ],
    },
    {
      question: "What is this number?",
      phonetic: "26",
      correctAnswer: "twenty-six",
      answers: [
        { buttonLabel: "visi haya", value: "twenty-six", sinhala: "විසි හය" },
        { buttonLabel: "visi aṭa", value: "twenty-eight", sinhala: "විසි අට" },
        { buttonLabel: "visi deka", value: "twenty-two", sinhala: "විසි දෙක" },
        {
          buttonLabel: "visi hatara",
          value: "twenty-four",
          sinhala: "විසි හතර",
        },
      ],
    },
    {
      question: "What is this number?",
      phonetic: "විසි හත",
      correctAnswer: "27",
      answers: [
        { buttonLabel: "27", value: "27" },
        { buttonLabel: "25", value: "25" },
        { buttonLabel: "29", value: "29" },
        { buttonLabel: "23", value: "23" },
      ],
    },
    {
      question: "What is this number?",
      phonetic: "27",
      correctAnswer: "twenty-seven",
      answers: [
        { buttonLabel: "visi hata", value: "twenty-seven", sinhala: "විසි හත" },
        { buttonLabel: "visi paha", value: "twenty-five", sinhala: "විසි පහ" },
        {
          buttonLabel: "visi namaya",
          value: "twenty-nine",
          sinhala: "විසි නමය",
        },
        {
          buttonLabel: "visi tuna",
          value: "twenty-three",
          sinhala: "විසි තුන",
        },
      ],
    },
    {
      question: "What is this number?",
      phonetic: "විසි අට",
      correctAnswer: "28",
      answers: [
        { buttonLabel: "28", value: "28" },
        { buttonLabel: "24", value: "24" },
        { buttonLabel: "22", value: "22" },
        { buttonLabel: "26", value: "26" },
      ],
    },
    {
      question: "What is this number?",
      phonetic: "28",
      correctAnswer: "twenty-eight",
      answers: [
        { buttonLabel: "visi aṭa", value: "twenty-eight", sinhala: "විසි අට" },
        {
          buttonLabel: "visi hatara",
          value: "twenty-four",
          sinhala: "විසි හතර",
        },
        { buttonLabel: "visi deka", value: "twenty-two", sinhala: "විසි දෙක" },
        { buttonLabel: "visi haya", value: "twenty-six", sinhala: "විසි හය" },
      ],
    },
    {
      question: "What is this number?",
      phonetic: "විසි නමය",
      correctAnswer: "29",
      answers: [
        { buttonLabel: "29", value: "29" },
        { buttonLabel: "27", value: "27" },
        { buttonLabel: "25", value: "25" },
        { buttonLabel: "23", value: "23" },
      ],
    },
    {
      question: "What is this number?",
      phonetic: "29",
      correctAnswer: "twenty-nine",
      answers: [
        {
          buttonLabel: "visi namaya",
          value: "twenty-nine",
          sinhala: "විසි නමය",
        },
        { buttonLabel: "visi hata", value: "twenty-seven", sinhala: "විසි හත" },
        { buttonLabel: "visi paha", value: "twenty-five", sinhala: "විසි පහ" },
        {
          buttonLabel: "visi tuna",
          value: "twenty-three",
          sinhala: "විසි තුන",
        },
      ],
    },
    {
      question: "What is this number?",
      phonetic: "තිහ",
      correctAnswer: "30",
      answers: [
        { buttonLabel: "30", value: "30" },
        { buttonLabel: "22", value: "22" },
        { buttonLabel: "28", value: "28" },
        { buttonLabel: "26", value: "26" },
      ],
    },
    {
      question: "What is this number?",
      phonetic: "30",
      correctAnswer: "thirty",
      answers: [
        { buttonLabel: "tiha", value: "thirty", sinhala: "තිහ" },
        { buttonLabel: "visi deka", value: "twenty-two", sinhala: "විසි දෙක" },
        { buttonLabel: "visi aṭa", value: "twenty-eight", sinhala: "විසි අට" },
        { buttonLabel: "visi haya", value: "twenty-six", sinhala: "විසි හය" },
      ],
    },
  ],
  [
    {
      question: "What is this number?",
      phonetic: "තිහ",
      correctAnswer: "30",
      answers: [
        { buttonLabel: "30", value: "30" },
        { buttonLabel: "35", value: "35" },
        { buttonLabel: "33", value: "33" },
        { buttonLabel: "36", value: "36" },
      ],
    },
    {
      question: "What is this number?",
      phonetic: "30",
      correctAnswer: "thirty",
      answers: [
        { buttonLabel: "tiha", value: "thirty", sinhala: "තිහ" },
        { buttonLabel: "tis paha", value: "thirty-five", sinhala: "තිස් පහ" },
        { buttonLabel: "tis tuna", value: "thirty-three", sinhala: "තිස් තුන" },
        { buttonLabel: "tis haya", value: "thirty-six", sinhala: "තිස් හය" },
      ],
    },
    {
      question: "What is this number?",
      phonetic: "තිස් එක",
      correctAnswer: "31",
      answers: [
        { buttonLabel: "31", value: "31" },
        { buttonLabel: "37", value: "37" },
        { buttonLabel: "39", value: "39" },
        { buttonLabel: "30", value: "30" },
      ],
    },
    {
      question: "What is this number?",
      phonetic: "31",
      correctAnswer: "thirty-one",
      answers: [
        { buttonLabel: "tis eka", value: "thirty-one", sinhala: "තිස් එක" },
        { buttonLabel: "tis hata", value: "thirty-seven", sinhala: "තිස් හත" },
        {
          buttonLabel: "tis namaya",
          value: "thirty-nine",
          sinhala: "තිස් නමය",
        },
        { buttonLabel: "tiha", value: "thirty", sinhala: "තිහ" },
      ],
    },
    {
      question: "What is this number?",
      phonetic: "තිස් දෙක",
      correctAnswer: "32",
      answers: [
        { buttonLabel: "32", value: "32" },
        { buttonLabel: "38", value: "38" },
        { buttonLabel: "34", value: "34" },
        { buttonLabel: "40", value: "40" },
      ],
    },
    {
      question: "What is this number?",
      phonetic: "32",
      correctAnswer: "thirty-two",
      answers: [
        { buttonLabel: "tis deka", value: "thirty-two", sinhala: "තිස් දෙක" },
        { buttonLabel: "tis aṭa", value: "thirty-eight", sinhala: "තිස් අට" },
        {
          buttonLabel: "tis hatara",
          value: "thirty-four",
          sinhala: "තිස් හතර",
        },
        { buttonLabel: "hataliha", value: "forty", sinhala: "හතලිහ" },
      ],
    },
    {
      question: "What is this number?",
      phonetic: "තිස් තුන",
      correctAnswer: "33",
      answers: [
        { buttonLabel: "33", value: "33" },
        { buttonLabel: "35", value: "35" },
        { buttonLabel: "37", value: "37" },
        { buttonLabel: "31", value: "31" },
      ],
    },
    {
      question: "What is this number?",
      phonetic: "33",
      correctAnswer: "thirty-three",
      answers: [
        { buttonLabel: "tis tuna", value: "thirty-three", sinhala: "තිස් තුන" },
        { buttonLabel: "tis paha", value: "thirty-five", sinhala: "තිස් පහ" },
        { buttonLabel: "tis hata", value: "thirty-seven", sinhala: "තිස් හත" },
        { buttonLabel: "tis eka", value: "thirty-one", sinhala: "තිස් එක" },
      ],
    },
    {
      question: "What is this number?",
      phonetic: "තිස් හතර",
      correctAnswer: "34",
      answers: [
        { buttonLabel: "34", value: "34" },
        { buttonLabel: "36", value: "36" },
        { buttonLabel: "32", value: "32" },
        { buttonLabel: "40", value: "40" },
      ],
    },
    {
      question: "What is this number?",
      phonetic: "34",
      correctAnswer: "thirty-four",
      answers: [
        {
          buttonLabel: "tis hatara",
          value: "thirty-four",
          sinhala: "තිස් හතර",
        },
        { buttonLabel: "tis haya", value: "thirty-six", sinhala: "තිස් හය" },
        { buttonLabel: "tis deka", value: "thirty-two", sinhala: "තිස් දෙක" },
        { buttonLabel: "hataliha", value: "forty", sinhala: "හතලිහ" },
      ],
    },
    {
      question: "What is this number?",
      phonetic: "තිස් පහ",
      correctAnswer: "35",
      answers: [
        { buttonLabel: "35", value: "35" },
        { buttonLabel: "39", value: "39" },
        { buttonLabel: "33", value: "33" },
        { buttonLabel: "37", value: "37" },
      ],
    },
    {
      question: "What is this number?",
      phonetic: "35",
      correctAnswer: "thirty-five",
      answers: [
        { buttonLabel: "tis paha", value: "thirty-five", sinhala: "තිස් පහ" },
        {
          buttonLabel: "tis namaya",
          value: "thirty-nine",
          sinhala: "තිස් නමය",
        },
        { buttonLabel: "tis tuna", value: "thirty-three", sinhala: "තිස් තුන" },
        { buttonLabel: "tis hata", value: "thirty-seven", sinhala: "තිස් හත" },
      ],
    },
    {
      question: "What is this number?",
      phonetic: "තිස් හය",
      correctAnswer: "36",
      answers: [
        { buttonLabel: "36", value: "36" },
        { buttonLabel: "38", value: "38" },
        { buttonLabel: "32", value: "32" },
        { buttonLabel: "34", value: "34" },
      ],
    },
    {
      question: "What is this number?",
      phonetic: "36",
      correctAnswer: "thirty-six",
      answers: [
        { buttonLabel: "tis haya", value: "thirty-six", sinhala: "තිස් හය" },
        { buttonLabel: "tis aṭa", value: "thirty-eight", sinhala: "තිස් අට" },
        { buttonLabel: "tis deka", value: "thirty-two", sinhala: "තිස් දෙක" },
        {
          buttonLabel: "tis hatara",
          value: "thirty-four",
          sinhala: "තිස් හතර",
        },
      ],
    },
    {
      question: "What is this number?",
      phonetic: "තිස් හත",
      correctAnswer: "37",
      answers: [
        { buttonLabel: "37", value: "37" },
        { buttonLabel: "35", value: "35" },
        { buttonLabel: "39", value: "39" },
        { buttonLabel: "33", value: "33" },
      ],
    },
    {
      question: "What is this number?",
      phonetic: "37",
      correctAnswer: "thirty-seven",
      answers: [
        { buttonLabel: "tis hata", value: "thirty-seven", sinhala: "තිස් හත" },
        { buttonLabel: "tis paha", value: "thirty-five", sinhala: "තිස් පහ" },
        {
          buttonLabel: "tis namaya",
          value: "thirty-nine",
          sinhala: "තිස් නමය",
        },
        { buttonLabel: "tis tuna", value: "thirty-three", sinhala: "තිස් තුන" },
      ],
    },
    {
      question: "What is this number?",
      phonetic: "තිස් අට",
      correctAnswer: "38",
      answers: [
        { buttonLabel: "38", value: "38" },
        { buttonLabel: "34", value: "34" },
        { buttonLabel: "32", value: "32" },
        { buttonLabel: "36", value: "36" },
      ],
    },
    {
      question: "What is this number?",
      phonetic: "38",
      correctAnswer: "thirty-eight",
      answers: [
        { buttonLabel: "tis aṭa", value: "thirty-eight", sinhala: "තිස් අට" },
        {
          buttonLabel: "tis hatara",
          value: "thirty-four",
          sinhala: "තිස් හතර",
        },
        { buttonLabel: "tis deka", value: "thirty-two", sinhala: "තිස් දෙක" },
        { buttonLabel: "tis haya", value: "thirty-six", sinhala: "තිස් හය" },
      ],
    },
    {
      question: "What is this number?",
      phonetic: "තිස් නමය",
      correctAnswer: "39",
      answers: [
        { buttonLabel: "39", value: "39" },
        { buttonLabel: "37", value: "37" },
        { buttonLabel: "35", value: "35" },
        { buttonLabel: "33", value: "33" },
      ],
    },
    {
      question: "What is this number?",
      phonetic: "39",
      correctAnswer: "thirty-nine",
      answers: [
        {
          buttonLabel: "tis namaya",
          value: "thirty-nine",
          sinhala: "තිස් නමය",
        },
        { buttonLabel: "tis hata", value: "thirty-seven", sinhala: "තිස් හත" },
        { buttonLabel: "tis paha", value: "thirty-five", sinhala: "තිස් පහ" },
        { buttonLabel: "tis tuna", value: "thirty-three", sinhala: "තිස් තුන" },
      ],
    },
    {
      question: "What is this number?",
      phonetic: "හතලිහ",
      correctAnswer: "40",
      answers: [
        { buttonLabel: "40", value: "40" },
        { buttonLabel: "32", value: "32" },
        { buttonLabel: "38", value: "38" },
        { buttonLabel: "36", value: "36" },
      ],
    },
    {
      question: "What is this number?",
      phonetic: "40",
      correctAnswer: "forty",
      answers: [
        { buttonLabel: "hataliha", value: "forty", sinhala: "හතලිහ" },
        { buttonLabel: "tis deka", value: "thirty-two", sinhala: "තිස් දෙක" },
        { buttonLabel: "tis aṭa", value: "thirty-eight", sinhala: "තිස් අට" },
        { buttonLabel: "tis haya", value: "thirty-six", sinhala: "තිස් හය" },
      ],
    },
  ],
  [
    {
      question: "What is this number?",
      phonetic: "හතලිහ",
      correctAnswer: "40",
      answers: [
        { buttonLabel: "40", value: "40" },
        { buttonLabel: "45", value: "45" },
        { buttonLabel: "43", value: "43" },
        { buttonLabel: "46", value: "46" },
      ],
    },
    {
      question: "What is this number?",
      phonetic: "40",
      correctAnswer: "forty",
      answers: [
        { buttonLabel: "hataliha", value: "forty", sinhala: "හතලිහ" },
        {
          buttonLabel: "hatalis paha",
          value: "forty-five",
          sinhala: "හතලිස් පහ",
        },
        {
          buttonLabel: "hatalis tuna",
          value: "forty-three",
          sinhala: "හතලිස් තුන",
        },
        {
          buttonLabel: "hatalis haya",
          value: "forty-six",
          sinhala: "හතලිස් හය",
        },
      ],
    },
    {
      question: "What is this number?",
      phonetic: "හතලිස් එක",
      correctAnswer: "41",
      answers: [
        { buttonLabel: "41", value: "41" },
        { buttonLabel: "47", value: "47" },
        { buttonLabel: "49", value: "49" },
        { buttonLabel: "40", value: "40" },
      ],
    },
    {
      question: "What is this number?",
      phonetic: "41",
      correctAnswer: "forty-one",
      answers: [
        {
          buttonLabel: "hatalis eka",
          value: "forty-one",
          sinhala: "හතලිස් එක",
        },
        {
          buttonLabel: "hatalis hata",
          value: "forty-seven",
          sinhala: "හතලිස් හත",
        },
        {
          buttonLabel: "hatalis namaya",
          value: "forty-nine",
          sinhala: "හතලිස් නමය",
        },
        { buttonLabel: "hataliha", value: "forty", sinhala: "හතලිහ" },
      ],
    },
    {
      question: "What is this number?",
      phonetic: "හතලිස් දෙක",
      correctAnswer: "42",
      answers: [
        { buttonLabel: "42", value: "42" },
        { buttonLabel: "48", value: "48" },
        { buttonLabel: "44", value: "44" },
        { buttonLabel: "50", value: "50" },
      ],
    },
    {
      question: "What is this number?",
      phonetic: "42",
      correctAnswer: "forty-two",
      answers: [
        {
          buttonLabel: "hatalis deka",
          value: "forty-two",
          sinhala: "හතලිස් දෙක",
        },
        {
          buttonLabel: "hatalis aṭa",
          value: "forty-eight",
          sinhala: "හතලිස් අට",
        },
        {
          buttonLabel: "hatalis hatara",
          value: "forty-four",
          sinhala: "හතලිස් හතර",
        },
        { buttonLabel: "panaha", value: "fifty", sinhala: "පනහ" },
      ],
    },
    {
      question: "What is this number?",
      phonetic: "හතලිස් තුන",
      correctAnswer: "43",
      answers: [
        { buttonLabel: "43", value: "43" },
        { buttonLabel: "45", value: "45" },
        { buttonLabel: "47", value: "47" },
        { buttonLabel: "41", value: "41" },
      ],
    },
    {
      question: "What is this number?",
      phonetic: "43",
      correctAnswer: "forty-three",
      answers: [
        {
          buttonLabel: "hatalis tuna",
          value: "forty-three",
          sinhala: "හතලිස් තුන",
        },
        {
          buttonLabel: "hatalis paha",
          value: "forty-five",
          sinhala: "හතලිස් පහ",
        },
        {
          buttonLabel: "hatalis hata",
          value: "forty-seven",
          sinhala: "හතලිස් හත",
        },
        {
          buttonLabel: "hatalis eka",
          value: "forty-one",
          sinhala: "හතලිස් එක",
        },
      ],
    },
    {
      question: "What is this number?",
      phonetic: "හතලිස් හතර",
      correctAnswer: "44",
      answers: [
        { buttonLabel: "44", value: "44" },
        { buttonLabel: "46", value: "46" },
        { buttonLabel: "42", value: "42" },
        { buttonLabel: "50", value: "50" },
      ],
    },
    {
      question: "What is this number?",
      phonetic: "44",
      correctAnswer: "forty-four",
      answers: [
        {
          buttonLabel: "hatalis hatara",
          value: "forty-four",
          sinhala: "හතලිස් හතර",
        },
        {
          buttonLabel: "hatalis haya",
          value: "forty-six",
          sinhala: "හතලිස් හය",
        },
        {
          buttonLabel: "hatalis deka",
          value: "forty-two",
          sinhala: "හතලිස් දෙක",
        },
        { buttonLabel: "panaha", value: "fifty", sinhala: "පනහ" },
      ],
    },
    {
      question: "What is this number?",
      phonetic: "හතලිස් පහ",
      correctAnswer: "45",
      answers: [
        { buttonLabel: "45", value: "45" },
        { buttonLabel: "49", value: "49" },
        { buttonLabel: "43", value: "43" },
        { buttonLabel: "47", value: "47" },
      ],
    },
    {
      question: "What is this number?",
      phonetic: "45",
      correctAnswer: "forty-five",
      answers: [
        {
          buttonLabel: "hatalis paha",
          value: "forty-five",
          sinhala: "හතලිස් පහ",
        },
        {
          buttonLabel: "hatalis namaya",
          value: "forty-nine",
          sinhala: "හතලිස් නමය",
        },
        {
          buttonLabel: "hatalis tuna",
          value: "forty-three",
          sinhala: "හතලිස් තුන",
        },
        {
          buttonLabel: "hatalis hata",
          value: "forty-seven",
          sinhala: "හතලිස් හත",
        },
      ],
    },
    {
      question: "What is this number?",
      phonetic: "හතලිස් හය",
      correctAnswer: "46",
      answers: [
        { buttonLabel: "46", value: "46" },
        { buttonLabel: "48", value: "48" },
        { buttonLabel: "42", value: "42" },
        { buttonLabel: "44", value: "44" },
      ],
    },
    {
      question: "What is this number?",
      phonetic: "46",
      correctAnswer: "forty-six",
      answers: [
        {
          buttonLabel: "hatalis haya",
          value: "forty-six",
          sinhala: "හතලිස් හය",
        },
        {
          buttonLabel: "hatalis aṭa",
          value: "forty-eight",
          sinhala: "හතලිස් අට",
        },
        {
          buttonLabel: "hatalis deka",
          value: "forty-two",
          sinhala: "හතලිස් දෙක",
        },
        {
          buttonLabel: "hatalis hatara",
          value: "forty-four",
          sinhala: "හතලිස් හතර",
        },
      ],
    },
    {
      question: "What is this number?",
      phonetic: "හතලිස් හත",
      correctAnswer: "47",
      answers: [
        { buttonLabel: "47", value: "47" },
        { buttonLabel: "45", value: "45" },
        { buttonLabel: "49", value: "49" },
        { buttonLabel: "43", value: "43" },
      ],
    },
    {
      question: "What is this number?",
      phonetic: "47",
      correctAnswer: "forty-seven",
      answers: [
        {
          buttonLabel: "hatalis hata",
          value: "forty-seven",
          sinhala: "හතලිස් හත",
        },
        {
          buttonLabel: "hatalis paha",
          value: "forty-five",
          sinhala: "හතලිස් පහ",
        },
        {
          buttonLabel: "hatalis namaya",
          value: "forty-nine",
          sinhala: "හතලිස් නමය",
        },
        {
          buttonLabel: "hatalis tuna",
          value: "forty-three",
          sinhala: "හතලිස් තුන",
        },
      ],
    },
    {
      question: "What is this number?",
      phonetic: "හතලිස් අට",
      correctAnswer: "48",
      answers: [
        { buttonLabel: "48", value: "48" },
        { buttonLabel: "44", value: "44" },
        { buttonLabel: "42", value: "42" },
        { buttonLabel: "46", value: "46" },
      ],
    },
    {
      question: "What is this number?",
      phonetic: "48",
      correctAnswer: "forty-eight",
      answers: [
        {
          buttonLabel: "hatalis aṭa",
          value: "forty-eight",
          sinhala: "හතලිස් අට",
        },
        {
          buttonLabel: "hatalis hatara",
          value: "forty-four",
          sinhala: "හතලිස් හතර",
        },
        {
          buttonLabel: "hatalis deka",
          value: "forty-two",
          sinhala: "හතලිස් දෙක",
        },
        {
          buttonLabel: "hatalis haya",
          value: "forty-six",
          sinhala: "හතලිස් හය",
        },
      ],
    },
    {
      question: "What is this number?",
      phonetic: "හතලිස් නමය",
      correctAnswer: "49",
      answers: [
        { buttonLabel: "49", value: "49" },
        { buttonLabel: "47", value: "47" },
        { buttonLabel: "45", value: "45" },
        { buttonLabel: "43", value: "43" },
      ],
    },
    {
      question: "What is this number?",
      phonetic: "49",
      correctAnswer: "forty-nine",
      answers: [
        {
          buttonLabel: "hatalis namaya",
          value: "forty-nine",
          sinhala: "හතලිස් නමය",
        },
        {
          buttonLabel: "hatalis hata",
          value: "forty-seven",
          sinhala: "හතලිස් හත",
        },
        {
          buttonLabel: "hatalis paha",
          value: "forty-five",
          sinhala: "හතලිස් පහ",
        },
        {
          buttonLabel: "hatalis tuna",
          value: "forty-three",
          sinhala: "හතලිස් තුන",
        },
      ],
    },
    {
      question: "What is this number?",
      phonetic: "පනහ",
      correctAnswer: "50",
      answers: [
        { buttonLabel: "50", value: "50" },
        { buttonLabel: "42", value: "42" },
        { buttonLabel: "48", value: "48" },
        { buttonLabel: "46", value: "46" },
      ],
    },
    {
      question: "What is this number?",
      phonetic: "50",
      correctAnswer: "fifty",
      answers: [
        { buttonLabel: "panaha", value: "fifty", sinhala: "පනහ" },
        {
          buttonLabel: "hatalis deka",
          value: "forty-two",
          sinhala: "හතලිස් දෙක",
        },
        {
          buttonLabel: "hatalis aṭa",
          value: "forty-eight",
          sinhala: "හතලිස් අට",
        },
        {
          buttonLabel: "hatalis haya",
          value: "forty-six",
          sinhala: "හතලිස් හය",
        },
      ],
    },
  ],
  [
    {
      question: "What is this number?",
      phonetic: "පනස් එක",
      correctAnswer: "51",
      answers: [
        { buttonLabel: "51", value: "51" },
        { buttonLabel: "55", value: "55" },
        { buttonLabel: "53", value: "53" },
        { buttonLabel: "56", value: "56" },
      ],
    },
    {
      question: "What is this number?",
      phonetic: "51",
      correctAnswer: "fifty-one",
      answers: [
        { buttonLabel: "panas eka", value: "fifty-one", sinhala: "පනස් එක" },
        { buttonLabel: "panas paha", value: "fifty-five", sinhala: "පනස් පහ" },
        {
          buttonLabel: "panas tuna",
          value: "fifty-three",
          sinhala: "පනස් තුන",
        },
        { buttonLabel: "panas haya", value: "fifty-six", sinhala: "පනස් හය" },
      ],
    },
    {
      question: "What is this number?",
      phonetic: "පනස් දෙක",
      correctAnswer: "52",
      answers: [
        { buttonLabel: "52", value: "52" },
        { buttonLabel: "57", value: "57" },
        { buttonLabel: "59", value: "59" },
        { buttonLabel: "51", value: "51" },
      ],
    },
    {
      question: "What is this number?",
      phonetic: "52",
      correctAnswer: "fifty-two",
      answers: [
        { buttonLabel: "panas deka", value: "fifty-two", sinhala: "පනස් දෙක" },
        { buttonLabel: "panas hata", value: "fifty-seven", sinhala: "පනස් හත" },
        {
          buttonLabel: "panas namaya",
          value: "fifty-nine",
          sinhala: "පනස් නමය",
        },
        { buttonLabel: "panas eka", value: "fifty-one", sinhala: "පනස් එක" },
      ],
    },
    {
      question: "What is this number?",
      phonetic: "පනස් තුන",
      correctAnswer: "53",
      answers: [
        { buttonLabel: "53", value: "53" },
        { buttonLabel: "58", value: "58" },
        { buttonLabel: "54", value: "54" },
        { buttonLabel: "60", value: "60" },
      ],
    },
    {
      question: "What is this number?",
      phonetic: "53",
      correctAnswer: "fifty-three",
      answers: [
        {
          buttonLabel: "panas tuna",
          value: "fifty-three",
          sinhala: "පනස් තුන",
        },
        { buttonLabel: "panas aṭa", value: "fifty-eight", sinhala: "පනස් අට" },
        {
          buttonLabel: "panas hatara",
          value: "fifty-four",
          sinhala: "පනස් හතර",
        },
        { buttonLabel: "hæṭa", value: "sixty", sinhala: "හැට" },
      ],
    },
    {
      question: "What is this number?",
      phonetic: "පනස් හතර",
      correctAnswer: "54",
      answers: [
        { buttonLabel: "54", value: "54" },
        { buttonLabel: "56", value: "56" },
        { buttonLabel: "52", value: "52" },
        { buttonLabel: "60", value: "60" },
      ],
    },
    {
      question: "What is this number?",
      phonetic: "54",
      correctAnswer: "fifty-four",
      answers: [
        {
          buttonLabel: "panas hatara",
          value: "fifty-four",
          sinhala: "පනස් හතර",
        },
        { buttonLabel: "panas haya", value: "fifty-six", sinhala: "පනස් හය" },
        { buttonLabel: "panas deka", value: "fifty-two", sinhala: "පනස් දෙක" },
        { buttonLabel: "hæṭa", value: "sixty", sinhala: "හැට" },
      ],
    },
    {
      question: "What is this number?",
      phonetic: "පනස් පහ",
      correctAnswer: "55",
      answers: [
        { buttonLabel: "55", value: "55" },
        { buttonLabel: "59", value: "59" },
        { buttonLabel: "53", value: "53" },
        { buttonLabel: "57", value: "57" },
      ],
    },
    {
      question: "What is this number?",
      phonetic: "55",
      correctAnswer: "fifty-five",
      answers: [
        { buttonLabel: "panas paha", value: "fifty-five", sinhala: "පනස් පහ" },
        {
          buttonLabel: "panas namaya",
          value: "fifty-nine",
          sinhala: "පනස් නමය",
        },
        {
          buttonLabel: "panas tuna",
          value: "fifty-three",
          sinhala: "පනස් තුන",
        },
        { buttonLabel: "panas hata", value: "fifty-seven", sinhala: "පනස් හත" },
      ],
    },
    {
      question: "What is this number?",
      phonetic: "පනස් හය",
      correctAnswer: "56",
      answers: [
        { buttonLabel: "56", value: "56" },
        { buttonLabel: "58", value: "58" },
        { buttonLabel: "52", value: "52" },
        { buttonLabel: "54", value: "54" },
      ],
    },
    {
      question: "What is this number?",
      phonetic: "56",
      correctAnswer: "fifty-six",
      answers: [
        { buttonLabel: "panas haya", value: "fifty-six", sinhala: "පනස් හය" },
        { buttonLabel: "panas aṭa", value: "fifty-eight", sinhala: "පනස් අට" },
        { buttonLabel: "panas deka", value: "fifty-two", sinhala: "පනස් දෙක" },
        {
          buttonLabel: "panas hatara",
          value: "fifty-four",
          sinhala: "පනස් හතර",
        },
      ],
    },
    {
      question: "What is this number?",
      phonetic: "පනස් හත",
      correctAnswer: "57",
      answers: [
        { buttonLabel: "57", value: "57" },
        { buttonLabel: "55", value: "55" },
        { buttonLabel: "59", value: "59" },
        { buttonLabel: "53", value: "53" },
      ],
    },
    {
      question: "What is this number?",
      phonetic: "57",
      correctAnswer: "fifty-seven",
      answers: [
        { buttonLabel: "panas hata", value: "fifty-seven", sinhala: "පනස් හත" },
        { buttonLabel: "panas paha", value: "fifty-five", sinhala: "පනස් පහ" },
        {
          buttonLabel: "panas namaya",
          value: "fifty-nine",
          sinhala: "පනස් නමය",
        },
        {
          buttonLabel: "panas tuna",
          value: "fifty-three",
          sinhala: "පනස් තුන",
        },
      ],
    },
    {
      question: "What is this number?",
      phonetic: "පනස් අට",
      correctAnswer: "58",
      answers: [
        { buttonLabel: "58", value: "58" },
        { buttonLabel: "54", value: "54" },
        { buttonLabel: "52", value: "52" },
        { buttonLabel: "56", value: "56" },
      ],
    },
    {
      question: "What is this number?",
      phonetic: "58",
      correctAnswer: "fifty-eight",
      answers: [
        { buttonLabel: "panas aṭa", value: "fifty-eight", sinhala: "පනස් අට" },
        {
          buttonLabel: "panas hatara",
          value: "fifty-four",
          sinhala: "පනස් හතර",
        },
        { buttonLabel: "panas deka", value: "fifty-two", sinhala: "පනස් දෙක" },
        { buttonLabel: "panas haya", value: "fifty-six", sinhala: "පනස් හය" },
      ],
    },
    {
      question: "What is this number?",
      phonetic: "පනස් නමය",
      correctAnswer: "59",
      answers: [
        { buttonLabel: "59", value: "59" },
        { buttonLabel: "57", value: "57" },
        { buttonLabel: "55", value: "55" },
        { buttonLabel: "53", value: "53" },
      ],
    },
    {
      question: "What is this number?",
      phonetic: "59",
      correctAnswer: "fifty-nine",
      answers: [
        {
          buttonLabel: "panas namaya",
          value: "fifty-nine",
          sinhala: "පනස් නමය",
        },
        { buttonLabel: "panas hata", value: "fifty-seven", sinhala: "පනස් හත" },
        { buttonLabel: "panas paha", value: "fifty-five", sinhala: "පනස් පහ" },
        {
          buttonLabel: "panas tuna",
          value: "fifty-three",
          sinhala: "පනස් තුන",
        },
      ],
    },
    {
      question: "What is this number?",
      phonetic: "හැට",
      correctAnswer: "60",
      answers: [
        { buttonLabel: "60", value: "60" },
        { buttonLabel: "52", value: "52" },
        { buttonLabel: "58", value: "58" },
        { buttonLabel: "56", value: "56" },
      ],
    },
    {
      question: "What is this number?",
      phonetic: "60",
      correctAnswer: "sixty",
      answers: [
        { buttonLabel: "hæṭa", value: "sixty", sinhala: "හැට" },
        { buttonLabel: "panas deka", value: "fifty-two", sinhala: "පනස් දෙක" },
        { buttonLabel: "panas aṭa", value: "fifty-eight", sinhala: "පනස් අට" },
        { buttonLabel: "panas haya", value: "fifty-six", sinhala: "පනස් හය" },
      ],
    },
  ],
  [
    {
      question: "What is this number?",
      phonetic: "හැට එක",
      correctAnswer: "61",
      answers: [
        { buttonLabel: "61", value: "61" },
        { buttonLabel: "65", value: "65" },
        { buttonLabel: "63", value: "63" },
        { buttonLabel: "66", value: "66" },
      ],
    },
    {
      question: "What is this number?",
      phonetic: "61",
      correctAnswer: "sixty-one",
      answers: [
        { buttonLabel: "hæṭa eka", value: "sixty-one", sinhala: "හැට එක" },
        { buttonLabel: "hæṭa paha", value: "sixty-five", sinhala: "හැට පහ" },
        { buttonLabel: "hæṭa tuna", value: "sixty-three", sinhala: "හැට තුන" },
        { buttonLabel: "hæṭa haya", value: "sixty-six", sinhala: "හැට හය" },
      ],
    },
    {
      question: "What is this number?",
      phonetic: "හැට දෙක",
      correctAnswer: "62",
      answers: [
        { buttonLabel: "62", value: "62" },
        { buttonLabel: "67", value: "67" },
        { buttonLabel: "69", value: "69" },
        { buttonLabel: "61", value: "61" },
      ],
    },
    {
      question: "What is this number?",
      phonetic: "62",
      correctAnswer: "sixty-two",
      answers: [
        { buttonLabel: "hæṭa deka", value: "sixty-two", sinhala: "හැට දෙක" },
        { buttonLabel: "hæṭa hata", value: "sixty-seven", sinhala: "හැට හත" },
        { buttonLabel: "hæṭa namaya", value: "sixty-nine", sinhala: "හැට නමය" },
        { buttonLabel: "hæṭa eka", value: "sixty-one", sinhala: "හැට එක" },
      ],
    },
    {
      question: "What is this number?",
      phonetic: "හැට තුන",
      correctAnswer: "63",
      answers: [
        { buttonLabel: "63", value: "63" },
        { buttonLabel: "68", value: "68" },
        { buttonLabel: "64", value: "64" },
        { buttonLabel: "70", value: "70" },
      ],
    },
    {
      question: "What is this number?",
      phonetic: "63",
      correctAnswer: "sixty-three",
      answers: [
        { buttonLabel: "hæṭa tuna", value: "sixty-three", sinhala: "හැට තුන" },
        { buttonLabel: "hæṭa aṭa", value: "sixty-eight", sinhala: "හැට අට" },
        { buttonLabel: "hæṭa hatara", value: "sixty-four", sinhala: "හැට හතර" },
        { buttonLabel: "hættǣva", value: "seventy", sinhala: "හැත්තෑව" },
      ],
    },
    {
      question: "What is this number?",
      phonetic: "හැට හතර",
      correctAnswer: "64",
      answers: [
        { buttonLabel: "64", value: "64" },
        { buttonLabel: "66", value: "66" },
        { buttonLabel: "62", value: "62" },
        { buttonLabel: "70", value: "70" },
      ],
    },
    {
      question: "What is this number?",
      phonetic: "64",
      correctAnswer: "sixty-four",
      answers: [
        { buttonLabel: "hæṭa hatara", value: "sixty-four", sinhala: "හැට හතර" },
        { buttonLabel: "hæṭa haya", value: "sixty-six", sinhala: "හැට හය" },
        { buttonLabel: "hæṭa deka", value: "sixty-two", sinhala: "හැට දෙක" },
        { buttonLabel: "hættǣva", value: "seventy", sinhala: "හැත්තෑව" },
      ],
    },
    {
      question: "What is this number?",
      phonetic: "හැට පහ",
      correctAnswer: "65",
      answers: [
        { buttonLabel: "65", value: "65" },
        { buttonLabel: "69", value: "69" },
        { buttonLabel: "63", value: "63" },
        { buttonLabel: "67", value: "67" },
      ],
    },
    {
      question: "What is this number?",
      phonetic: "65",
      correctAnswer: "sixty-five",
      answers: [
        { buttonLabel: "hæṭa paha", value: "sixty-five", sinhala: "හැට පහ" },
        { buttonLabel: "hæṭa namaya", value: "sixty-nine", sinhala: "හැට නමය" },
        { buttonLabel: "hæṭa tuna", value: "sixty-three", sinhala: "හැට තුන" },
        { buttonLabel: "hæṭa hata", value: "sixty-seven", sinhala: "හැට හත" },
      ],
    },
    {
      question: "What is this number?",
      phonetic: "හැට හය",
      correctAnswer: "66",
      answers: [
        { buttonLabel: "66", value: "66" },
        { buttonLabel: "68", value: "68" },
        { buttonLabel: "62", value: "62" },
        { buttonLabel: "64", value: "64" },
      ],
    },
    {
      question: "What is this number?",
      phonetic: "66",
      correctAnswer: "sixty-six",
      answers: [
        { buttonLabel: "hæṭa haya", value: "sixty-six", sinhala: "හැට හය" },
        { buttonLabel: "hæṭa aṭa", value: "sixty-eight", sinhala: "හැට අට" },
        { buttonLabel: "hæṭa deka", value: "sixty-two", sinhala: "හැට දෙක" },
        { buttonLabel: "hæṭa hatara", value: "sixty-four", sinhala: "හැට හතර" },
      ],
    },
    {
      question: "What is this number?",
      phonetic: "හැට හත",
      correctAnswer: "67",
      answers: [
        { buttonLabel: "67", value: "67" },
        { buttonLabel: "65", value: "65" },
        { buttonLabel: "69", value: "69" },
        { buttonLabel: "63", value: "63" },
      ],
    },
    {
      question: "What is this number?",
      phonetic: "67",
      correctAnswer: "sixty-seven",
      answers: [
        { buttonLabel: "hæṭa hata", value: "sixty-seven", sinhala: "හැට හත" },
        { buttonLabel: "hæṭa paha", value: "sixty-five", sinhala: "හැට පහ" },
        { buttonLabel: "hæṭa namaya", value: "sixty-nine", sinhala: "හැට නමය" },
        { buttonLabel: "hæṭa tuna", value: "sixty-three", sinhala: "හැට තුන" },
      ],
    },
    {
      question: "What is this number?",
      phonetic: "හැට අට",
      correctAnswer: "68",
      answers: [
        { buttonLabel: "68", value: "68" },
        { buttonLabel: "64", value: "64" },
        { buttonLabel: "62", value: "62" },
        { buttonLabel: "66", value: "66" },
      ],
    },
    {
      question: "What is this number?",
      phonetic: "68",
      correctAnswer: "sixty-eight",
      answers: [
        { buttonLabel: "hæṭa aṭa", value: "sixty-eight", sinhala: "හැට අට" },
        { buttonLabel: "hæṭa hatara", value: "sixty-four", sinhala: "හැට හතර" },
        { buttonLabel: "hæṭa deka", value: "sixty-two", sinhala: "හැට දෙක" },
        { buttonLabel: "hæṭa haya", value: "sixty-six", sinhala: "හැට හය" },
      ],
    },
    {
      question: "What is this number?",
      phonetic: "හැට නමය",
      correctAnswer: "69",
      answers: [
        { buttonLabel: "69", value: "69" },
        { buttonLabel: "67", value: "67" },
        { buttonLabel: "65", value: "65" },
        { buttonLabel: "63", value: "63" },
      ],
    },
    {
      question: "What is this number?",
      phonetic: "69",
      correctAnswer: "sixty-nine",
      answers: [
        { buttonLabel: "hæṭa namaya", value: "sixty-nine", sinhala: "හැට නමය" },
        { buttonLabel: "hæṭa hata", value: "sixty-seven", sinhala: "හැට හත" },
        { buttonLabel: "hæṭa paha", value: "sixty-five", sinhala: "හැට පහ" },
        { buttonLabel: "hæṭa tuna", value: "sixty-three", sinhala: "හැට තුන" },
      ],
    },
    {
      question: "What is this number?",
      phonetic: "හැත්තෑව",
      correctAnswer: "70",
      answers: [
        { buttonLabel: "70", value: "70" },
        { buttonLabel: "62", value: "62" },
        { buttonLabel: "68", value: "68" },
        { buttonLabel: "66", value: "66" },
      ],
    },
    {
      question: "What is this number?",
      phonetic: "70",
      correctAnswer: "seventy",
      answers: [
        { buttonLabel: "hættǣva", value: "seventy", sinhala: "හැත්තෑව" },
        { buttonLabel: "hæṭa deka", value: "sixty-two", sinhala: "හැට දෙක" },
        { buttonLabel: "hæṭa aṭa", value: "sixty-eight", sinhala: "හැට අට" },
        { buttonLabel: "hæṭa haya", value: "sixty-six", sinhala: "හැට හය" },
      ],
    },
  ],
  [
    {
      question: "What is this number?",
      phonetic: "හැත්ත එක",
      correctAnswer: "71",
      answers: [
        { buttonLabel: "71", value: "71" },
        { buttonLabel: "75", value: "75" },
        { buttonLabel: "73", value: "73" },
        { buttonLabel: "76", value: "76" },
      ],
    },
    {
      question: "What is this number?",
      phonetic: "71",
      correctAnswer: "seventy-one",
      answers: [
        { buttonLabel: "hætta eka", value: "seventy-one", sinhala: "හැත්ත එක" },
        {
          buttonLabel: "hætta paha",
          value: "seventy-five",
          sinhala: "හැත්ත පහ",
        },
        {
          buttonLabel: "hætta tuna",
          value: "seventy-three",
          sinhala: "හැත්ත තුන",
        },
        {
          buttonLabel: "hætta haya",
          value: "seventy-six",
          sinhala: "හැත්ත හය",
        },
      ],
    },
    {
      question: "What is this number?",
      phonetic: "හැත්ත දෙක",
      correctAnswer: "72",
      answers: [
        { buttonLabel: "72", value: "72" },
        { buttonLabel: "77", value: "77" },
        { buttonLabel: "79", value: "79" },
        { buttonLabel: "71", value: "71" },
      ],
    },
    {
      question: "What is this number?",
      phonetic: "72",
      correctAnswer: "seventy-two",
      answers: [
        {
          buttonLabel: "hætta deka",
          value: "seventy-two",
          sinhala: "හැත්ත දෙක",
        },
        {
          buttonLabel: "hætta hata",
          value: "seventy-seven",
          sinhala: "හැත්ත හත",
        },
        {
          buttonLabel: "hætta namaya",
          value: "seventy-nine",
          sinhala: "හැත්ත නමය",
        },
        { buttonLabel: "hætta eka", value: "seventy-one", sinhala: "හැත්ත එක" },
      ],
    },
    {
      question: "What is this number?",
      phonetic: "හැත්ත තුන",
      correctAnswer: "73",
      answers: [
        { buttonLabel: "73", value: "73" },
        { buttonLabel: "78", value: "78" },
        { buttonLabel: "74", value: "74" },
        { buttonLabel: "80", value: "80" },
      ],
    },
    {
      question: "What is this number?",
      phonetic: "73",
      correctAnswer: "seventy-three",
      answers: [
        {
          buttonLabel: "hætta tuna",
          value: "seventy-three",
          sinhala: "හැත්ත තුන",
        },
        {
          buttonLabel: "hætta aṭa",
          value: "seventy-eight",
          sinhala: "හැත්ත අට",
        },
        {
          buttonLabel: "hætta hatara",
          value: "seventy-four",
          sinhala: "හැත්ත හතර",
        },
        { buttonLabel: "asūva", value: "eighty", sinhala: "අසූව" },
      ],
    },
    {
      question: "What is this number?",
      phonetic: "හැත්ත හතර",
      correctAnswer: "74",
      answers: [
        { buttonLabel: "74", value: "74" },
        { buttonLabel: "76", value: "76" },
        { buttonLabel: "72", value: "72" },
        { buttonLabel: "80", value: "80" },
      ],
    },
    {
      question: "What is this number?",
      phonetic: "74",
      correctAnswer: "seventy-four",
      answers: [
        {
          buttonLabel: "hætta hatara",
          value: "seventy-four",
          sinhala: "හැත්ත හතර",
        },
        {
          buttonLabel: "hætta haya",
          value: "seventy-six",
          sinhala: "හැත්ත හය",
        },
        {
          buttonLabel: "hætta deka",
          value: "seventy-two",
          sinhala: "හැත්ත දෙක",
        },
        { buttonLabel: "asūva", value: "eighty", sinhala: "අසූව" },
      ],
    },
    {
      question: "What is this number?",
      phonetic: "හැත්ත පහ",
      correctAnswer: "75",
      answers: [
        { buttonLabel: "75", value: "75" },
        { buttonLabel: "79", value: "79" },
        { buttonLabel: "73", value: "73" },
        { buttonLabel: "77", value: "77" },
      ],
    },
    {
      question: "What is this number?",
      phonetic: "75",
      correctAnswer: "seventy-five",
      answers: [
        {
          buttonLabel: "hætta paha",
          value: "seventy-five",
          sinhala: "හැත්ත පහ",
        },
        {
          buttonLabel: "hætta namaya",
          value: "seventy-nine",
          sinhala: "හැත්ත නමය",
        },
        {
          buttonLabel: "hætta tuna",
          value: "seventy-three",
          sinhala: "හැත්ත තුන",
        },
        {
          buttonLabel: "hætta hata",
          value: "seventy-seven",
          sinhala: "හැත්ත හත",
        },
      ],
    },
    {
      question: "What is this number?",
      phonetic: "හැත්ත හය",
      correctAnswer: "76",
      answers: [
        { buttonLabel: "76", value: "76" },
        { buttonLabel: "78", value: "78" },
        { buttonLabel: "72", value: "72" },
        { buttonLabel: "74", value: "74" },
      ],
    },
    {
      question: "What is this number?",
      phonetic: "76",
      correctAnswer: "seventy-six",
      answers: [
        {
          buttonLabel: "hætta haya",
          value: "seventy-six",
          sinhala: "හැත්ත හය",
        },
        {
          buttonLabel: "hætta aṭa",
          value: "seventy-eight",
          sinhala: "හැත්ත අට",
        },
        {
          buttonLabel: "hætta deka",
          value: "seventy-two",
          sinhala: "හැත්ත දෙක",
        },
        {
          buttonLabel: "hætta hatara",
          value: "seventy-four",
          sinhala: "හැත්ත හතර",
        },
      ],
    },
    {
      question: "What is this number?",
      phonetic: "හැත්ත හත",
      correctAnswer: "77",
      answers: [
        { buttonLabel: "77", value: "77" },
        { buttonLabel: "75", value: "75" },
        { buttonLabel: "79", value: "79" },
        { buttonLabel: "73", value: "73" },
      ],
    },
    {
      question: "What is this number?",
      phonetic: "77",
      correctAnswer: "seventy-seven",
      answers: [
        {
          buttonLabel: "hætta hata",
          value: "seventy-seven",
          sinhala: "හැත්ත හත",
        },
        {
          buttonLabel: "hætta paha",
          value: "seventy-five",
          sinhala: "හැත්ත පහ",
        },
        {
          buttonLabel: "hætta namaya",
          value: "seventy-nine",
          sinhala: "හැත්ත නමය",
        },
        {
          buttonLabel: "hætta tuna",
          value: "seventy-three",
          sinhala: "හැත්ත තුන",
        },
      ],
    },
    {
      question: "What is this number?",
      phonetic: "හැත්ත අට",
      correctAnswer: "78",
      answers: [
        { buttonLabel: "78", value: "78" },
        { buttonLabel: "74", value: "74" },
        { buttonLabel: "72", value: "72" },
        { buttonLabel: "76", value: "76" },
      ],
    },
    {
      question: "What is this number?",
      phonetic: "78",
      correctAnswer: "seventy-eight",
      answers: [
        {
          buttonLabel: "hætta aṭa",
          value: "seventy-eight",
          sinhala: "හැත්ත අට",
        },
        {
          buttonLabel: "hætta hatara",
          value: "seventy-four",
          sinhala: "හැත්ත හතර",
        },
        {
          buttonLabel: "hætta deka",
          value: "seventy-two",
          sinhala: "හැත්ත දෙක",
        },
        {
          buttonLabel: "hætta haya",
          value: "seventy-six",
          sinhala: "හැත්ත හය",
        },
      ],
    },
    {
      question: "What is this number?",
      phonetic: "හැත්ත නමය",
      correctAnswer: "79",
      answers: [
        { buttonLabel: "79", value: "79" },
        { buttonLabel: "77", value: "77" },
        { buttonLabel: "75", value: "75" },
        { buttonLabel: "73", value: "73" },
      ],
    },
    {
      question: "What is this number?",
      phonetic: "79",
      correctAnswer: "seventy-nine",
      answers: [
        {
          buttonLabel: "hætta namaya",
          value: "seventy-nine",
          sinhala: "හැත්ත නමය",
        },
        {
          buttonLabel: "hætta hata",
          value: "seventy-seven",
          sinhala: "හැත්ත හත",
        },
        {
          buttonLabel: "hætta paha",
          value: "seventy-five",
          sinhala: "හැත්ත පහ",
        },
        {
          buttonLabel: "hætta tuna",
          value: "seventy-three",
          sinhala: "හැත්ත තුන",
        },
      ],
    },
    {
      question: "What is this number?",
      phonetic: "අසූව",
      correctAnswer: "80",
      answers: [
        { buttonLabel: "80", value: "80" },
        { buttonLabel: "72", value: "72" },
        { buttonLabel: "78", value: "78" },
        { buttonLabel: "76", value: "76" },
      ],
    },
    {
      question: "What is this number?",
      phonetic: "80",
      correctAnswer: "eighty",
      answers: [
        { buttonLabel: "asūva", value: "eighty", sinhala: "අසූව" },
        {
          buttonLabel: "hætta deka",
          value: "seventy-two",
          sinhala: "හැත්ත දෙක",
        },
        {
          buttonLabel: "hætta aṭa",
          value: "seventy-eight",
          sinhala: "හැත්ත අට",
        },
        {
          buttonLabel: "hætta haya",
          value: "seventy-six",
          sinhala: "හැත්ත හය",
        },
      ],
    },
  ],
  [
    {
      question: "What is this number?",
      phonetic: "අසූව",
      correctAnswer: "80",
      answers: [
        { buttonLabel: "80", value: "80" },
        { buttonLabel: "72", value: "72" },
        { buttonLabel: "78", value: "78" },
        { buttonLabel: "76", value: "76" },
      ],
    },
    {
      question: "What is this number?",
      phonetic: "80",
      correctAnswer: "eighty",
      answers: [
        { buttonLabel: "asūva", value: "eighty", sinhala: "අසූව" },
        {
          buttonLabel: "hætta deka",
          value: "seventy-two",
          sinhala: "හැත්ත දෙක",
        },
        {
          buttonLabel: "hætta aṭa",
          value: "seventy-eight",
          sinhala: "හැත්ත අට",
        },
        {
          buttonLabel: "hætta haya",
          value: "seventy-six",
          sinhala: "හැත්ත හය",
        },
      ],
    },
    {
      question: "What is this number?",
      phonetic: "අසූ එක",
      correctAnswer: "81",
      answers: [
        { buttonLabel: "81", value: "81" },
        { buttonLabel: "85", value: "85" },
        { buttonLabel: "83", value: "83" },
        { buttonLabel: "86", value: "86" },
      ],
    },
    {
      question: "What is this number?",
      phonetic: "81",
      correctAnswer: "eighty-one",
      answers: [
        { buttonLabel: "asū eka", value: "eighty-one", sinhala: "අසූ එක" },
        { buttonLabel: "asū paha", value: "eighty-five", sinhala: "අසූ පහ" },
        { buttonLabel: "asū tuna", value: "eighty-three", sinhala: "අසූ තුන" },
        { buttonLabel: "asū haya", value: "eighty-six", sinhala: "අසූ හය" },
      ],
    },
    {
      question: "What is this number?",
      phonetic: "අසූ දෙක",
      correctAnswer: "82",
      answers: [
        { buttonLabel: "82", value: "82" },
        { buttonLabel: "87", value: "87" },
        { buttonLabel: "89", value: "89" },
        { buttonLabel: "81", value: "81" },
      ],
    },
    {
      question: "What is this number?",
      phonetic: "82",
      correctAnswer: "eighty-two",
      answers: [
        { buttonLabel: "asū deka", value: "eighty-two", sinhala: "අසූ දෙක" },
        { buttonLabel: "asū hata", value: "eighty-seven", sinhala: "අසූ හත" },
        { buttonLabel: "asū namaya", value: "eighty-nine", sinhala: "අසූ නමය" },
        { buttonLabel: "asū eka", value: "eighty-one", sinhala: "අසූ එක" },
      ],
    },
    {
      question: "What is this number?",
      phonetic: "අසූ තුන",
      correctAnswer: "83",
      answers: [
        { buttonLabel: "83", value: "83" },
        { buttonLabel: "88", value: "88" },
        { buttonLabel: "84", value: "84" },
        { buttonLabel: "90", value: "90" },
      ],
    },
    {
      question: "What is this number?",
      phonetic: "83",
      correctAnswer: "eighty-three",
      answers: [
        { buttonLabel: "asū tuna", value: "eighty-three", sinhala: "අසූ තුන" },
        { buttonLabel: "asū aṭa", value: "eighty-eight", sinhala: "අසූ අට" },
        { buttonLabel: "asū hatara", value: "eighty-four", sinhala: "අසූ හතර" },
        { buttonLabel: "anūva", value: "ninety", sinhala: "අනූව" },
      ],
    },
    {
      question: "What is this number?",
      phonetic: "අසූ හතර",
      correctAnswer: "84",
      answers: [
        { buttonLabel: "84", value: "84" },
        { buttonLabel: "86", value: "86" },
        { buttonLabel: "82", value: "82" },
        { buttonLabel: "90", value: "90" },
      ],
    },
    {
      question: "What is this number?",
      phonetic: "84",
      correctAnswer: "eighty-four",
      answers: [
        { buttonLabel: "asū hatara", value: "eighty-four", sinhala: "අසූ හතර" },
        { buttonLabel: "asū haya", value: "eighty-six", sinhala: "අසූ හය" },
        { buttonLabel: "asū deka", value: "eighty-two", sinhala: "අසූ දෙක" },
        { buttonLabel: "anūva", value: "ninety", sinhala: "අනූව" },
      ],
    },
    {
      question: "What is this number?",
      phonetic: "අසූ පහ",
      correctAnswer: "85",
      answers: [
        { buttonLabel: "85", value: "85" },
        { buttonLabel: "89", value: "89" },
        { buttonLabel: "83", value: "83" },
        { buttonLabel: "87", value: "87" },
      ],
    },
    {
      question: "What is this number?",
      phonetic: "85",
      correctAnswer: "eighty-five",
      answers: [
        { buttonLabel: "asū paha", value: "eighty-five", sinhala: "අසූ පහ" },
        { buttonLabel: "asū namaya", value: "eighty-nine", sinhala: "අසූ නමය" },
        { buttonLabel: "asū tuna", value: "eighty-three", sinhala: "අසූ තුන" },
        { buttonLabel: "asū hata", value: "eighty-seven", sinhala: "අසූ හත" },
      ],
    },
    {
      question: "What is this number?",
      phonetic: "අසූ හය",
      correctAnswer: "86",
      answers: [
        { buttonLabel: "86", value: "86" },
        { buttonLabel: "88", value: "88" },
        { buttonLabel: "82", value: "82" },
        { buttonLabel: "84", value: "84" },
      ],
    },
    {
      question: "What is this number?",
      phonetic: "86",
      correctAnswer: "eighty-six",
      answers: [
        { buttonLabel: "asū haya", value: "eighty-six", sinhala: "අසූ හය" },
        { buttonLabel: "asū aṭa", value: "eighty-eight", sinhala: "අසූ අට" },
        { buttonLabel: "asū deka", value: "eighty-two", sinhala: "අසූ දෙක" },
        { buttonLabel: "asū hatara", value: "eighty-four", sinhala: "අසූ හතර" },
      ],
    },
    {
      question: "What is this number?",
      phonetic: "අසූ හත",
      correctAnswer: "87",
      answers: [
        { buttonLabel: "87", value: "87" },
        { buttonLabel: "85", value: "85" },
        { buttonLabel: "89", value: "89" },
        { buttonLabel: "83", value: "83" },
      ],
    },
    {
      question: "What is this number?",
      phonetic: "87",
      correctAnswer: "eighty-seven",
      answers: [
        { buttonLabel: "asū hata", value: "eighty-seven", sinhala: "අසූ හත" },
        { buttonLabel: "asū paha", value: "eighty-five", sinhala: "අසූ පහ" },
        { buttonLabel: "asū namaya", value: "eighty-nine", sinhala: "අසූ නමය" },
        { buttonLabel: "asū tuna", value: "eighty-three", sinhala: "අසූ තුන" },
      ],
    },
    {
      question: "What is this number?",
      phonetic: "අසූ අට",
      correctAnswer: "88",
      answers: [
        { buttonLabel: "88", value: "88" },
        { buttonLabel: "84", value: "84" },
        { buttonLabel: "82", value: "82" },
        { buttonLabel: "86", value: "86" },
      ],
    },
    {
      question: "What is this number?",
      phonetic: "88",
      correctAnswer: "eighty-eight",
      answers: [
        { buttonLabel: "asū aṭa", value: "eighty-eight", sinhala: "අසූ අට" },
        { buttonLabel: "asū hatara", value: "eighty-four", sinhala: "අසූ හතර" },
        { buttonLabel: "asū deka", value: "eighty-two", sinhala: "අසූ දෙක" },
        { buttonLabel: "asū haya", value: "eighty-six", sinhala: "අසූ හය" },
      ],
    },
    {
      question: "What is this number?",
      phonetic: "අසූ නමය",
      correctAnswer: "89",
      answers: [
        { buttonLabel: "89", value: "89" },
        { buttonLabel: "87", value: "87" },
        { buttonLabel: "85", value: "85" },
        { buttonLabel: "83", value: "83" },
      ],
    },
    {
      question: "What is this number?",
      phonetic: "89",
      correctAnswer: "eighty-nine",
      answers: [
        { buttonLabel: "asū namaya", value: "eighty-nine", sinhala: "අසූ නමය" },
        { buttonLabel: "asū hata", value: "eighty-seven", sinhala: "අසූ හත" },
        { buttonLabel: "asū paha", value: "eighty-five", sinhala: "අසූ පහ" },
        { buttonLabel: "asū tuna", value: "eighty-three", sinhala: "අසූ තුන" },
      ],
    },
    {
      question: "What is this number?",
      phonetic: "අනූව",
      correctAnswer: "90",
      answers: [
        { buttonLabel: "90", value: "90" },
        { buttonLabel: "82", value: "82" },
        { buttonLabel: "88", value: "88" },
        { buttonLabel: "86", value: "86" },
      ],
    },
    {
      question: "What is this number?",
      phonetic: "90",
      correctAnswer: "ninety",
      answers: [
        { buttonLabel: "anūva", value: "ninety", sinhala: "අනූව" },
        { buttonLabel: "asū deka", value: "eighty-two", sinhala: "අසූ දෙක" },
        { buttonLabel: "asū aṭa", value: "eighty-eight", sinhala: "අසූ අට" },
        { buttonLabel: "asū haya", value: "eighty-six", sinhala: "අසූ හය" },
      ],
    },
  ],
  [
    {
      question: "What is this number?",
      phonetic: "අනූව",
      correctAnswer: "90",
      answers: [
        { buttonLabel: "90", value: "90" },
        { buttonLabel: "82", value: "82" },
        { buttonLabel: "88", value: "88" },
        { buttonLabel: "86", value: "86" },
      ],
    },
    {
      question: "What is this number?",
      phonetic: "90",
      correctAnswer: "ninety",
      answers: [
        { buttonLabel: "anūva", value: "ninety", sinhala: "අනූව" },
        { buttonLabel: "asū deka", value: "eighty-two", sinhala: "අසූ දෙක" },
        { buttonLabel: "asū aṭa", value: "eighty-eight", sinhala: "අසූ අට" },
        { buttonLabel: "asū haya", value: "eighty-six", sinhala: "අසූ හය" },
      ],
    },
    {
      question: "What is this number?",
      phonetic: "අනූ එක",
      correctAnswer: "91",
      answers: [
        { buttonLabel: "91", value: "91" },
        { buttonLabel: "95", value: "95" },
        { buttonLabel: "93", value: "93" },
        { buttonLabel: "96", value: "96" },
      ],
    },
    {
      question: "What is this number?",
      phonetic: "91",
      correctAnswer: "ninety-one",
      answers: [
        { buttonLabel: "anū eka", value: "ninety-one", sinhala: "අනූ එක" },
        { buttonLabel: "anū paha", value: "ninety-five", sinhala: "අනූ පහ" },
        { buttonLabel: "anū tuna", value: "ninety-three", sinhala: "අනූ තුන" },
        { buttonLabel: "anū haya", value: "ninety-six", sinhala: "අනූ හය" },
      ],
    },
    {
      question: "What is this number?",
      phonetic: "අනූ දෙක",
      correctAnswer: "92",
      answers: [
        { buttonLabel: "92", value: "92" },
        { buttonLabel: "97", value: "97" },
        { buttonLabel: "99", value: "99" },
        { buttonLabel: "91", value: "91" },
      ],
    },
    {
      question: "What is this number?",
      phonetic: "92",
      correctAnswer: "ninety-two",
      answers: [
        { buttonLabel: "anū deka", value: "ninety-two", sinhala: "අනූ දෙක" },
        { buttonLabel: "anū hata", value: "ninety-seven", sinhala: "අනූ හත" },
        { buttonLabel: "anū namaya", value: "ninety-nine", sinhala: "අනූ නමය" },
        { buttonLabel: "anū eka", value: "ninety-one", sinhala: "අනූ එක" },
      ],
    },
    {
      question: "What is this number?",
      phonetic: "අනූ තුන",
      correctAnswer: "93",
      answers: [
        { buttonLabel: "93", value: "93" },
        { buttonLabel: "98", value: "98" },
        { buttonLabel: "94", value: "94" },
        { buttonLabel: "100", value: "100" },
      ],
    },
    {
      question: "What is this number?",
      phonetic: "93",
      correctAnswer: "ninety-three",
      answers: [
        { buttonLabel: "anū tuna", value: "ninety-three", sinhala: "අනූ තුන" },
        { buttonLabel: "anū aṭa", value: "ninety-eight", sinhala: "අනූ අට" },
        { buttonLabel: "anū hatara", value: "ninety-four", sinhala: "අනූ හතර" },
        { buttonLabel: "sīya", value: "one hundred", sinhala: "සීය" },
      ],
    },
    {
      question: "What is this number?",
      phonetic: "අනූ හතර",
      correctAnswer: "94",
      answers: [
        { buttonLabel: "94", value: "94" },
        { buttonLabel: "96", value: "96" },
        { buttonLabel: "92", value: "92" },
        { buttonLabel: "100", value: "100" },
      ],
    },
    {
      question: "What is this number?",
      phonetic: "94",
      correctAnswer: "ninety-four",
      answers: [
        { buttonLabel: "anū hatara", value: "ninety-four", sinhala: "අනූ හතර" },
        { buttonLabel: "anū haya", value: "ninety-six", sinhala: "අනූ හය" },
        { buttonLabel: "anū deka", value: "ninety-two", sinhala: "අනූ දෙක" },
        { buttonLabel: "sīya", value: "one hundred", sinhala: "සීය" },
      ],
    },
    {
      question: "What is this number?",
      phonetic: "අනූ පහ",
      correctAnswer: "95",
      answers: [
        { buttonLabel: "95", value: "95" },
        { buttonLabel: "99", value: "99" },
        { buttonLabel: "93", value: "93" },
        { buttonLabel: "97", value: "97" },
      ],
    },
    {
      question: "What is this number?",
      phonetic: "95",
      correctAnswer: "ninety-five",
      answers: [
        { buttonLabel: "anū paha", value: "ninety-five", sinhala: "අනූ පහ" },
        { buttonLabel: "anū namaya", value: "ninety-nine", sinhala: "අනූ නමය" },
        { buttonLabel: "anū tuna", value: "ninety-three", sinhala: "අනූ තුන" },
        { buttonLabel: "anū hata", value: "ninety-seven", sinhala: "අනූ හත" },
      ],
    },
    {
      question: "What is this number?",
      phonetic: "අනූ හය",
      correctAnswer: "96",
      answers: [
        { buttonLabel: "96", value: "96" },
        { buttonLabel: "98", value: "98" },
        { buttonLabel: "92", value: "92" },
        { buttonLabel: "94", value: "94" },
      ],
    },
    {
      question: "What is this number?",
      phonetic: "96",
      correctAnswer: "ninety-six",
      answers: [
        { buttonLabel: "anū haya", value: "ninety-six", sinhala: "අනූ හය" },
        { buttonLabel: "anū aṭa", value: "ninety-eight", sinhala: "අනූ අට" },
        { buttonLabel: "anū deka", value: "ninety-two", sinhala: "අනූ දෙක" },
        { buttonLabel: "anū hatara", value: "ninety-four", sinhala: "අනූ හතර" },
      ],
    },
    {
      question: "What is this number?",
      phonetic: "අනූ හත",
      correctAnswer: "97",
      answers: [
        { buttonLabel: "97", value: "97" },
        { buttonLabel: "95", value: "95" },
        { buttonLabel: "99", value: "99" },
        { buttonLabel: "93", value: "93" },
      ],
    },
    {
      question: "What is this number?",
      phonetic: "97",
      correctAnswer: "ninety-seven",
      answers: [
        { buttonLabel: "anū hata", value: "ninety-seven", sinhala: "අනූ හත" },
        { buttonLabel: "anū paha", value: "ninety-five", sinhala: "අනූ පහ" },
        { buttonLabel: "anū namaya", value: "ninety-nine", sinhala: "අනූ නමය" },
        { buttonLabel: "anū tuna", value: "ninety-three", sinhala: "අනූ තුන" },
      ],
    },
    {
      question: "What is this number?",
      phonetic: "අනූ අට",
      correctAnswer: "98",
      answers: [
        { buttonLabel: "98", value: "98" },
        { buttonLabel: "94", value: "94" },
        { buttonLabel: "92", value: "92" },
        { buttonLabel: "96", value: "96" },
      ],
    },
    {
      question: "What is this number?",
      phonetic: "98",
      correctAnswer: "ninety-eight",
      answers: [
        { buttonLabel: "anū aṭa", value: "ninety-eight", sinhala: "අනූ අට" },
        { buttonLabel: "anū hatara", value: "ninety-four", sinhala: "අනූ හතර" },
        { buttonLabel: "anū deka", value: "ninety-two", sinhala: "අනූ දෙක" },
        { buttonLabel: "anū haya", value: "ninety-six", sinhala: "අනූ හය" },
      ],
    },
    {
      question: "What is this number?",
      phonetic: "අනූ නමය",
      correctAnswer: "99",
      answers: [
        { buttonLabel: "99", value: "99" },
        { buttonLabel: "97", value: "97" },
        { buttonLabel: "95", value: "95" },
        { buttonLabel: "93", value: "93" },
      ],
    },
    {
      question: "What is this number?",
      phonetic: "99",
      correctAnswer: "ninety-nine",
      answers: [
        { buttonLabel: "anū namaya", value: "ninety-nine", sinhala: "අනූ නමය" },
        { buttonLabel: "anū hata", value: "ninety-seven", sinhala: "අනූ හත" },
        { buttonLabel: "anū paha", value: "ninety-five", sinhala: "අනූ පහ" },
        { buttonLabel: "anū tuna", value: "ninety-three", sinhala: "අනූ තුන" },
      ],
    },
    {
      question: "What is this number?",
      phonetic: "එකසීය",
      correctAnswer: "100",
      answers: [
        { buttonLabel: "100", value: "100" },
        { buttonLabel: "92", value: "92" },
        { buttonLabel: "98", value: "98" },
        { buttonLabel: "96", value: "96" },
      ],
    },
    {
      question: "What is this number?",
      phonetic: "100",
      correctAnswer: "one hundred",
      answers: [
        { buttonLabel: "ekasīya", value: "one hundred", sinhala: "එකසීය" },
        { buttonLabel: "anū deka", value: "ninety-two", sinhala: "අනූ දෙක" },
        { buttonLabel: "anū aṭa", value: "ninety-eight", sinhala: "අනූ අට" },
        { buttonLabel: "anū haya", value: "ninety-six", sinhala: "අනූ හය" },
      ],
    },
    {
      question: "What is this number?",
      phonetic: "සීය",
      correctAnswer: "100",
      answers: [
        { buttonLabel: "100", value: "100" },
        { buttonLabel: "92", value: "92" },
        { buttonLabel: "98", value: "98" },
        { buttonLabel: "96", value: "96" },
      ],
    },
    {
      question: "What is this number?",
      phonetic: "100",
      correctAnswer: "one hundred",
      answers: [
        { buttonLabel: "sīya", value: "one hundred", sinhala: "සීය" },
        { buttonLabel: "anū deka", value: "ninety-two", sinhala: "අනූ දෙක" },
        { buttonLabel: "anū aṭa", value: "ninety-eight", sinhala: "අනූ අට" },
        { buttonLabel: "anū haya", value: "ninety-six", sinhala: "අනූ හය" },
      ],
    },
  ],
  [
    {
      question: "What is this number?",
      phonetic: "සීය",
      correctAnswer: "100",
      answers: [
        { buttonLabel: "100", value: "100" },
        { buttonLabel: "300", value: "300" },
        { buttonLabel: "200", value: "200" },
        { buttonLabel: "400", value: "400" },
      ],
    },
    {
      question: "What is this number?",
      phonetic: "100",
      correctAnswer: "one hundred",
      answers: [
        { buttonLabel: "sīya", value: "one hundred", sinhala: "සීය" },
        { buttonLabel: "tunsīya", value: "three hundred", sinhala: "තුන්සීය" },
        { buttonLabel: "desīya", value: "two hundred", sinhala: "දෙසීය" },
        { buttonLabel: "harasīya", value: "four hundred", sinhala: "හරසීය" },
      ],
    },
    {
      question: "What is this number?",
      phonetic: "එකසීය",
      correctAnswer: "100",
      answers: [
        { buttonLabel: "100", value: "100" },
        { buttonLabel: "300", value: "300" },
        { buttonLabel: "200", value: "200" },
        { buttonLabel: "400", value: "400" },
      ],
    },
    {
      question: "What is this number?",
      phonetic: "100",
      correctAnswer: "one hundred",
      answers: [
        { buttonLabel: "ekasīya", value: "one hundred", sinhala: "එකසීය" },
        { buttonLabel: "tunsīya", value: "three hundred", sinhala: "තුන්සීය" },
        { buttonLabel: "desīya", value: "two hundred", sinhala: "දෙසීය" },
        { buttonLabel: "harasīya", value: "four hundred", sinhala: "හරසීය" },
      ],
    },
    {
      question: "What is this number?",
      phonetic: "දෙසීය",
      correctAnswer: "200",
      answers: [
        { buttonLabel: "200", value: "200" },
        { buttonLabel: "600", value: "600" },
        { buttonLabel: "400", value: "400" },
        { buttonLabel: "500", value: "500" },
      ],
    },
    {
      question: "What is this number?",
      phonetic: "200",
      correctAnswer: "two hundred",
      answers: [
        { buttonLabel: "desīya", value: "two hundred", sinhala: "දෙසීය" },
        { buttonLabel: "hayasīya", value: "six hundred", sinhala: "හයසීය" },
        { buttonLabel: "harasīya", value: "four hundred", sinhala: "හරසීය" },
        { buttonLabel: "pansīya", value: "five hundred", sinhala: "පන්සීය" },
      ],
    },
    {
      question: "What is this number?",
      phonetic: "තුන්සීය",
      correctAnswer: "300",
      answers: [
        { buttonLabel: "300", value: "300" },
        { buttonLabel: "700", value: "700" },
        { buttonLabel: "900", value: "900" },
        { buttonLabel: "100", value: "100" },
      ],
    },
    {
      question: "What is this number?",
      phonetic: "300",
      correctAnswer: "three hundred",
      answers: [
        { buttonLabel: "tunsīya", value: "three hundred", sinhala: "තුන්සීය" },
        { buttonLabel: "hatsīya", value: "seven hundred", sinhala: "හත්සීය" },
        { buttonLabel: "namasīya", value: "nine hundred", sinhala: "නමසීය" },
        { buttonLabel: "ekasīya", value: "one hundred", sinhala: "එකසීය" },
      ],
    },
    {
      question: "What is this number?",
      phonetic: "හරසීය",
      correctAnswer: "400",
      answers: [
        { buttonLabel: "400", value: "400" },
        { buttonLabel: "800", value: "800" },
        { buttonLabel: "600", value: "600" },
        { buttonLabel: "200", value: "200" },
      ],
    },
    {
      question: "What is this number?",
      phonetic: "400",
      correctAnswer: "four hundred",
      answers: [
        { buttonLabel: "harasīya", value: "four hundred", sinhala: "හරසීය" },
        { buttonLabel: "aṭasīya", value: "eight hundred", sinhala: "අටසීය" },
        { buttonLabel: "hayasīya", value: "six hundred", sinhala: "හයසීය" },
        { buttonLabel: "desīya", value: "two hundred", sinhala: "දෙසීය" },
      ],
    },
    {
      question: "What is this number?",
      phonetic: "පන්සීය",
      correctAnswer: "500",
      answers: [
        { buttonLabel: "500", value: "500" },
        { buttonLabel: "900", value: "900" },
        { buttonLabel: "700", value: "700" },
        { buttonLabel: "300", value: "300" },
      ],
    },
    {
      question: "What is this number?",
      phonetic: "500",
      correctAnswer: "five hundred",
      answers: [
        { buttonLabel: "pansīya", value: "five hundred", sinhala: "පන්සීය" },
        { buttonLabel: "namasīya", value: "nine hundred", sinhala: "නමසීය" },
        { buttonLabel: "hatsīya", value: "seven hundred", sinhala: "හත්සීය" },
        { buttonLabel: "tunsīya", value: "three hundred", sinhala: "තුන්සීය" },
      ],
    },
    {
      question: "What is this number?",
      phonetic: "හයසීය",
      correctAnswer: "600",
      answers: [
        { buttonLabel: "600", value: "600" },
        { buttonLabel: "800", value: "800" },
        { buttonLabel: "400", value: "400" },
        { buttonLabel: "200", value: "200" },
      ],
    },
    {
      question: "What is this number?",
      phonetic: "600",
      correctAnswer: "six hundred",
      answers: [
        { buttonLabel: "hayasīya", value: "six hundred", sinhala: "හයසීය" },
        { buttonLabel: "aṭasīya", value: "eight hundred", sinhala: "අටසීය" },
        { buttonLabel: "harasīya", value: "four hundred", sinhala: "හරසීය" },
        { buttonLabel: "desīya", value: "two hundred", sinhala: "දෙසීය" },
      ],
    },
    {
      question: "What is this number?",
      phonetic: "හත්සීය",
      correctAnswer: "700",
      answers: [
        { buttonLabel: "700", value: "700" },
        { buttonLabel: "500", value: "500" },
        { buttonLabel: "900", value: "900" },
        { buttonLabel: "300", value: "300" },
      ],
    },
    {
      question: "What is this number?",
      phonetic: "700",
      correctAnswer: "seven hundred",
      answers: [
        { buttonLabel: "hatsīya", value: "seven hundred", sinhala: "හත්සීය" },
        { buttonLabel: "pansīya", value: "five hundred", sinhala: "පන්සීය" },
        { buttonLabel: "namasīya", value: "nine hundred", sinhala: "නමසීය" },
        { buttonLabel: "tunsīya", value: "three hundred", sinhala: "තුන්සීය" },
      ],
    },
    {
      question: "What is this number?",
      phonetic: "අටසීය",
      correctAnswer: "800",
      answers: [
        { buttonLabel: "800", value: "800" },
        { buttonLabel: "400", value: "400" },
        { buttonLabel: "600", value: "600" },
        { buttonLabel: "900", value: "900" },
      ],
    },
    {
      question: "What is this number?",
      phonetic: "800",
      correctAnswer: "eight hundred",
      answers: [
        { buttonLabel: "aṭasīya", value: "eight hundred", sinhala: "අටසීය" },
        { buttonLabel: "harasīya", value: "four hundred", sinhala: "හරසීය" },
        { buttonLabel: "hayasīya", value: "six hundred", sinhala: "හයසීය" },
        { buttonLabel: "namasīya", value: "nine hundred", sinhala: "නමසීය" },
      ],
    },
    {
      question: "What is this number?",
      phonetic: "නමසීය",
      correctAnswer: "900",
      answers: [
        { buttonLabel: "900", value: "900" },
        { buttonLabel: "700", value: "700" },
        { buttonLabel: "500", value: "500" },
        { buttonLabel: "300", value: "300" },
      ],
    },
    {
      question: "What is this number?",
      phonetic: "900",
      correctAnswer: "nine hundred",
      answers: [
        { buttonLabel: "namasīya", value: "nine hundred", sinhala: "නමසීය" },
        { buttonLabel: "hatsīya", value: "seven hundred", sinhala: "හත්සීය" },
        { buttonLabel: "pansīya", value: "five hundred", sinhala: "පන්සීය" },
        { buttonLabel: "tunsīya", value: "three hundred", sinhala: "තුන්සීය" },
      ],
    },
    {
      question: "What is this number?",
      phonetic: "දාහ",
      correctAnswer: "1000",
      answers: [
        { buttonLabel: "1000", value: "1000" },
        { buttonLabel: "400", value: "400" },
        { buttonLabel: "600", value: "600" },
        { buttonLabel: "900", value: "900" },
      ],
    },
    {
      question: "What is this number?",
      phonetic: "1000",
      correctAnswer: "one thousand",
      answers: [
        { buttonLabel: "dāha", value: "one thousand", sinhala: "දාහ" },
        { buttonLabel: "harasīya", value: "four hundred", sinhala: "හරසීය" },
        { buttonLabel: "hayasīya", value: "six hundred", sinhala: "හයසීය" },
        { buttonLabel: "namasīya", value: "nine hundred", sinhala: "නමසීය" },
      ],
    },
    {
      question: "What is this number?",
      phonetic: "එකදාහ",
      correctAnswer: "1000",
      answers: [
        { buttonLabel: "1000", value: "1000" },
        { buttonLabel: "400", value: "400" },
        { buttonLabel: "600", value: "600" },
        { buttonLabel: "900", value: "900" },
      ],
    },
    {
      question: "What is this number?",
      phonetic: "1000",
      correctAnswer: "one thousand",
      answers: [
        { buttonLabel: "ekadāha", value: "one thousand", sinhala: "එකදාහ" },
        { buttonLabel: "harasīya", value: "four hundred", sinhala: "හරසීය" },
        { buttonLabel: "hayasīya", value: "six hundred", sinhala: "හයසීය" },
        { buttonLabel: "namasīya", value: "nine hundred", sinhala: "නමසීය" },
      ],
    },
  ],
  [
    {
      question: "What is this number?",
      phonetic: "දාහ",
      correctAnswer: "1000",
      answers: [
        { buttonLabel: "1000", value: "1000" },
        { buttonLabel: "3000", value: "3000" },
        { buttonLabel: "2000", value: "2000" },
        { buttonLabel: "4000", value: "4000" },
      ],
    },
    {
      question: "What is this number?",
      phonetic: "1000",
      correctAnswer: "one thousand",
      answers: [
        { buttonLabel: "dāha", value: "one thousand", sinhala: "දාහ" },
        { buttonLabel: "tundāha", value: "three thousand", sinhala: "තුන්දාහ" },
        { buttonLabel: "dedāha", value: "two thousand", sinhala: "දෙදාහ" },
        { buttonLabel: "haradāha", value: "four thousand", sinhala: "හරදාහ" },
      ],
    },
    {
      question: "What is this number?",
      phonetic: "එකදාහ",
      correctAnswer: "1000",
      answers: [
        { buttonLabel: "1000", value: "1000" },
        { buttonLabel: "3000", value: "3000" },
        { buttonLabel: "2000", value: "2000" },
        { buttonLabel: "4000", value: "4000" },
      ],
    },
    {
      question: "What is this number?",
      phonetic: "1000",
      correctAnswer: "one thousand",
      answers: [
        { buttonLabel: "ekadāha", value: "one thousand", sinhala: "එකදාහ" },
        { buttonLabel: "tundāha", value: "three thousand", sinhala: "තුන්දාහ" },
        { buttonLabel: "dedāha", value: "two thousand", sinhala: "දෙදාහ" },
        { buttonLabel: "haradāha", value: "four thousand", sinhala: "හරදාහ" },
      ],
    },
    {
      question: "What is this number?",
      phonetic: "දෙදාහ",
      correctAnswer: "2000",
      answers: [
        { buttonLabel: "2000", value: "2000" },
        { buttonLabel: "6000", value: "6000" },
        { buttonLabel: "4000", value: "4000" },
        { buttonLabel: "5000", value: "5000" },
      ],
    },
    {
      question: "What is this number?",
      phonetic: "2000",
      correctAnswer: "two thousand",
      answers: [
        { buttonLabel: "dedāha", value: "two thousand", sinhala: "දෙදාහ" },
        { buttonLabel: "hayadāha", value: "six thousand", sinhala: "හයදාහ" },
        { buttonLabel: "haradāha", value: "four thousand", sinhala: "හරදාහ" },
        { buttonLabel: "pandāha", value: "five thousand", sinhala: "පන්දාහ" },
      ],
    },
    {
      question: "What is this number?",
      phonetic: "තුන්දාහ",
      correctAnswer: "3000",
      answers: [
        { buttonLabel: "3000", value: "3000" },
        { buttonLabel: "7000", value: "7000" },
        { buttonLabel: "9000", value: "9000" },
        { buttonLabel: "1000", value: "1000" },
      ],
    },
    {
      question: "What is this number?",
      phonetic: "3000",
      correctAnswer: "three thousand",
      answers: [
        { buttonLabel: "tundāha", value: "three thousand", sinhala: "තුන්දාහ" },
        { buttonLabel: "hatdāha", value: "seven thousand", sinhala: "හත්දාහ" },
        { buttonLabel: "namadāha", value: "nine thousand", sinhala: "නමදාහ" },
        { buttonLabel: "ekadāha", value: "one thousand", sinhala: "එකදාහ" },
      ],
    },
    {
      question: "What is this number?",
      phonetic: "හරදාහ",
      correctAnswer: "4000",
      answers: [
        { buttonLabel: "4000", value: "4000" },
        { buttonLabel: "8000", value: "8000" },
        { buttonLabel: "6000", value: "6000" },
        { buttonLabel: "2000", value: "2000" },
      ],
    },
    {
      question: "What is this number?",
      phonetic: "4000",
      correctAnswer: "four thousand",
      answers: [
        { buttonLabel: "haradāha", value: "four thousand", sinhala: "හරදාහ" },
        { buttonLabel: "aṭadāha", value: "eight thousand", sinhala: "අටදාහ" },
        { buttonLabel: "hayadāha", value: "six thousand", sinhala: "හයදාහ" },
        { buttonLabel: "dedāha", value: "two thousand", sinhala: "දෙදාහ" },
      ],
    },
    {
      question: "What is this number?",
      phonetic: "පන්දාහ",
      correctAnswer: "5000",
      answers: [
        { buttonLabel: "5000", value: "5000" },
        { buttonLabel: "9000", value: "9000" },
        { buttonLabel: "7000", value: "7000" },
        { buttonLabel: "3000", value: "3000" },
      ],
    },
    {
      question: "What is this number?",
      phonetic: "5000",
      correctAnswer: "five thousand",
      answers: [
        { buttonLabel: "pandāha", value: "five thousand", sinhala: "පන්දාහ" },
        { buttonLabel: "namadāha", value: "nine thousand", sinhala: "නමදාහ" },
        { buttonLabel: "hatdāha", value: "seven thousand", sinhala: "හත්දාහ" },
        { buttonLabel: "tundāha", value: "three thousand", sinhala: "තුන්දාහ" },
      ],
    },
    {
      question: "What is this number?",
      phonetic: "හයදාහ",
      correctAnswer: "6000",
      answers: [
        { buttonLabel: "6000", value: "6000" },
        { buttonLabel: "8000", value: "8000" },
        { buttonLabel: "4000", value: "4000" },
        { buttonLabel: "2000", value: "2000" },
      ],
    },
    {
      question: "What is this number?",
      phonetic: "6000",
      correctAnswer: "six thousand",
      answers: [
        { buttonLabel: "hayadāha", value: "six thousand", sinhala: "හයදාහ" },
        { buttonLabel: "aṭadāha", value: "eight thousand", sinhala: "අටදාහ" },
        { buttonLabel: "haradāha", value: "four thousand", sinhala: "හරදාහ" },
        { buttonLabel: "dedāha", value: "two thousand", sinhala: "දෙදාහ" },
      ],
    },
    {
      question: "What is this number?",
      phonetic: "හත්දාහ",
      correctAnswer: "7000",
      answers: [
        { buttonLabel: "7000", value: "7000" },
        { buttonLabel: "5000", value: "5000" },
        { buttonLabel: "9000", value: "9000" },
        { buttonLabel: "3000", value: "3000" },
      ],
    },
    {
      question: "What is this number?",
      phonetic: "7000",
      correctAnswer: "seven thousand",
      answers: [
        { buttonLabel: "hatdāha", value: "seven thousand", sinhala: "හත්දාහ" },
        { buttonLabel: "pandāha", value: "five thousand", sinhala: "පන්දාහ" },
        { buttonLabel: "namadāha", value: "nine thousand", sinhala: "නමදාහ" },
        { buttonLabel: "tundāha", value: "three thousand", sinhala: "තුන්දාහ" },
      ],
    },
    {
      question: "What is this number?",
      phonetic: "අටදාහ",
      correctAnswer: "8000",
      answers: [
        { buttonLabel: "8000", value: "8000" },
        { buttonLabel: "4000", value: "4000" },
        { buttonLabel: "6000", value: "6000" },
        { buttonLabel: "9000", value: "9000" },
      ],
    },
    {
      question: "What is this number?",
      phonetic: "8000",
      correctAnswer: "eight thousand",
      answers: [
        { buttonLabel: "aṭadāha", value: "eight thousand", sinhala: "අටදාහ" },
        { buttonLabel: "haradāha", value: "four thousand", sinhala: "හරදාහ" },
        { buttonLabel: "hayadāha", value: "six thousand", sinhala: "හයදාහ" },
        { buttonLabel: "namadāha", value: "nine thousand", sinhala: "නමදාහ" },
      ],
    },
    {
      question: "What is this number?",
      phonetic: "නමදාහ",
      correctAnswer: "9000",
      answers: [
        { buttonLabel: "9000", value: "9000" },
        { buttonLabel: "7000", value: "7000" },
        { buttonLabel: "5000", value: "5000" },
        { buttonLabel: "3000", value: "3000" },
      ],
    },
    {
      question: "What is this number?",
      phonetic: "9000",
      correctAnswer: "nine thousand",
      answers: [
        { buttonLabel: "namadāha", value: "nine thousand", sinhala: "නමදාහ" },
        { buttonLabel: "hatdāha", value: "seven thousand", sinhala: "හත්දාහ" },
        { buttonLabel: "pandāha", value: "five thousand", sinhala: "පන්දාහ" },
        { buttonLabel: "tundāha", value: "three thousand", sinhala: "තුන්දාහ" },
      ],
    },
    {
      question: "What is this number?",
      phonetic: "දහදාහ",
      correctAnswer: "10000",
      answers: [
        { buttonLabel: "10000", value: "10000" },
        { buttonLabel: "4000", value: "4000" },
        { buttonLabel: "6000", value: "6000" },
        { buttonLabel: "9000", value: "9000" },
      ],
    },
    {
      question: "What is this number?",
      phonetic: "10000",
      correctAnswer: "ten thousand",
      answers: [
        { buttonLabel: "dahadāha", value: "ten thousand", sinhala: "දහදාහ" },
        { buttonLabel: "haradāha", value: "four thousand", sinhala: "හරදාහ" },
        { buttonLabel: "hayadāha", value: "six thousand", sinhala: "හයදාහ" },
        { buttonLabel: "namadāha", value: "nine thousand", sinhala: "නමදාහ" },
      ],
    },
  ],
  [
    {
      question: "What is this number?",
      phonetic: "දහදාහ",
      correctAnswer: "10000",
      answers: [
        { buttonLabel: "10000", value: "10000" },
        { buttonLabel: "4000", value: "4000" },
        { buttonLabel: "6000", value: "6000" },
        { buttonLabel: "9000", value: "9000" },
      ],
    },
    {
      question: "What is this number?",
      phonetic: "10000",
      correctAnswer: "ten thousand",
      answers: [
        { buttonLabel: "dahadāha", value: "ten thousand", sinhala: "දහදාහ" },
        { buttonLabel: "haradāha", value: "four thousand", sinhala: "හරදාහ" },
        { buttonLabel: "hayadāha", value: "six thousand", sinhala: "හයදාහ" },
        { buttonLabel: "namadāha", value: "nine thousand", sinhala: "නමදාහ" },
      ],
    },
    {
      question: "What is this number?",
      phonetic: "එකොළොස්දාහ",
      correctAnswer: "11000",
      answers: [
        { buttonLabel: "11000", value: "11000" },
        { buttonLabel: "13000", value: "13000" },
        { buttonLabel: "12000", value: "12000" },
        { buttonLabel: "14000", value: "14000" },
      ],
    },
    {
      question: "What is this number?",
      phonetic: "11000",
      correctAnswer: "eleven thousand",
      answers: [
        {
          buttonLabel: "ekoḷosdāha",
          value: "eleven thousand",
          sinhala: "එකොළොස්දාහ",
        },
        {
          buttonLabel: "dahatundāha",
          value: "thirteen thousand",
          sinhala: "දහතුන්දාහ",
        },
        {
          buttonLabel: "doḷosdāha",
          value: "twelve thousand",
          sinhala: "දොළොස්දාහ",
        },
        {
          buttonLabel: "dahataradāha",
          value: "fourteen thousand",
          sinhala: "දහතර දාහ",
        },
      ],
    },
    {
      question: "What is this number?",
      phonetic: "දොළොස්දාහ",
      correctAnswer: "12000",
      answers: [
        { buttonLabel: "12000", value: "12000" },
        { buttonLabel: "16000", value: "16000" },
        { buttonLabel: "14000", value: "14000" },
        { buttonLabel: "15000", value: "15000" },
      ],
    },
    {
      question: "What is this number?",
      phonetic: "12000",
      correctAnswer: "twelve thousand",
      answers: [
        {
          buttonLabel: "doḷosdāha",
          value: "twelve thousand",
          sinhala: "දොළොස්දාහ",
        },
        {
          buttonLabel: "dasayadāha",
          value: "sixteen thousand",
          sinhala: "දසයදාහ",
        },
        {
          buttonLabel: "dahataradāha",
          value: "fourteen thousand",
          sinhala: "දහතර දාහ",
        },
        {
          buttonLabel: "pahaḷosdāha",
          value: "fifteen thousand",
          sinhala: "පහළොස්දාහ",
        },
      ],
    },
    {
      question: "What is this number?",
      phonetic: "දහතුන්දාහ",
      correctAnswer: "13000",
      answers: [
        { buttonLabel: "13000", value: "13000" },
        { buttonLabel: "17000", value: "17000" },
        { buttonLabel: "19000", value: "19000" },
        { buttonLabel: "11000", value: "11000" },
      ],
    },
    {
      question: "What is this number?",
      phonetic: "13000",
      correctAnswer: "thirteen thousand",
      answers: [
        {
          buttonLabel: "dahatundāha",
          value: "thirteen thousand",
          sinhala: "දහතුන්දාහ",
        },
        {
          buttonLabel: "dahatdāha",
          value: "seventeen thousand",
          sinhala: "දහත්දාහ",
        },
        {
          buttonLabel: "dahanamadāha",
          value: "nineteen thousand",
          sinhala: "දහනමදාහ",
        },
        {
          buttonLabel: "ekoḷosdāha",
          value: "eleven thousand",
          sinhala: "එකොළොස්දාහ",
        },
      ],
    },
    {
      question: "What is this number?",
      phonetic: "දහතර දාහ",
      correctAnswer: "14000",
      answers: [
        { buttonLabel: "14000", value: "14000" },
        { buttonLabel: "18000", value: "18000" },
        { buttonLabel: "16000", value: "16000" },
        { buttonLabel: "12000", value: "12000" },
      ],
    },
    {
      question: "What is this number?",
      phonetic: "14000",
      correctAnswer: "fourteen thousand",
      answers: [
        {
          buttonLabel: "dahataradāha",
          value: "fourteen thousand",
          sinhala: "දහතර දාහ",
        },
        {
          buttonLabel: "dahaaṭadāha",
          value: "eighteen thousand",
          sinhala: "දහඅටදාහ",
        },
        {
          buttonLabel: "dasayadāha",
          value: "sixteen thousand",
          sinhala: "දසයදාහ",
        },
        {
          buttonLabel: "doḷosdāha",
          value: "twelve thousand",
          sinhala: "දොළොස්දාහ",
        },
      ],
    },
    {
      question: "What is this number?",
      phonetic: "පහළොස්දාහ",
      correctAnswer: "15000",
      answers: [
        { buttonLabel: "15000", value: "15000" },
        { buttonLabel: "19000", value: "19000" },
        { buttonLabel: "13000", value: "13000" },
        { buttonLabel: "17000", value: "17000" },
      ],
    },
    {
      question: "What is this number?",
      phonetic: "15000",
      correctAnswer: "fifteen thousand",
      answers: [
        {
          buttonLabel: "pahaḷosdāha",
          value: "fifteen thousand",
          sinhala: "පහළොස්දාහ",
        },
        {
          buttonLabel: "dahanamadāha",
          value: "nineteen thousand",
          sinhala: "දහනමදාහ",
        },
        {
          buttonLabel: "dahatundāha",
          value: "thirteen thousand",
          sinhala: "දහතුන්දාහ",
        },
        {
          buttonLabel: "dahatdāha",
          value: "seventeen thousand",
          sinhala: "දහත්දාහ",
        },
      ],
    },
    {
      question: "What is this number?",
      phonetic: "දසයදාහ",
      correctAnswer: "16000",
      answers: [
        { buttonLabel: "16000", value: "16000" },
        { buttonLabel: "18000", value: "18000" },
        { buttonLabel: "12000", value: "12000" },
        { buttonLabel: "14000", value: "14000" },
      ],
    },
    {
      question: "What is this number?",
      phonetic: "16000",
      correctAnswer: "sixteen thousand",
      answers: [
        {
          buttonLabel: "dasayadāha",
          value: "sixteen thousand",
          sinhala: "දසයදාහ",
        },
        {
          buttonLabel: "dahaaṭadāha",
          value: "eighteen thousand",
          sinhala: "දහඅටදාහ",
        },
        {
          buttonLabel: "doḷosdāha",
          value: "twelve thousand",
          sinhala: "දොළොස්දාහ",
        },
        {
          buttonLabel: "dahataradāha",
          value: "fourteen thousand",
          sinhala: "දහතර දාහ",
        },
      ],
    },
    {
      question: "What is this number?",
      phonetic: "දහත්දාහ",
      correctAnswer: "17000",
      answers: [
        { buttonLabel: "17000", value: "17000" },
        { buttonLabel: "15000", value: "15000" },
        { buttonLabel: "19000", value: "19000" },
        { buttonLabel: "13000", value: "13000" },
      ],
    },
    {
      question: "What is this number?",
      phonetic: "17000",
      correctAnswer: "seventeen thousand",
      answers: [
        {
          buttonLabel: "dahatdāha",
          value: "seventeen thousand",
          sinhala: "දහත්දාහ",
        },
        {
          buttonLabel: "pahaḷosdāha",
          value: "fifteen thousand",
          sinhala: "පහළොස්දාහ",
        },
        {
          buttonLabel: "dahanamadāha",
          value: "nineteen thousand",
          sinhala: "දහනමදාහ",
        },
        {
          buttonLabel: "dahatundāha",
          value: "thirteen thousand",
          sinhala: "දහතුන්දාහ",
        },
      ],
    },
    {
      question: "What is this number?",
      phonetic: "දහඅටදාහ",
      correctAnswer: "18000",
      answers: [
        { buttonLabel: "18000", value: "18000" },
        { buttonLabel: "14000", value: "14000" },
        { buttonLabel: "12000", value: "12000" },
        { buttonLabel: "16000", value: "16000" },
      ],
    },
    {
      question: "What is this number?",
      phonetic: "18000",
      correctAnswer: "eighteen thousand",
      answers: [
        {
          buttonLabel: "dahaaṭadāha",
          value: "eighteen thousand",
          sinhala: "දහඅටදාහ",
        },
        {
          buttonLabel: "dahataradāha",
          value: "fourteen thousand",
          sinhala: "දහතර දාහ",
        },
        {
          buttonLabel: "doḷosdāha",
          value: "twelve thousand",
          sinhala: "දොළොස්දාහ",
        },
        {
          buttonLabel: "dasayadāha",
          value: "sixteen thousand",
          sinhala: "දසයදාහ",
        },
      ],
    },
    {
      question: "What is this number?",
      phonetic: "දහනමදාහ",
      correctAnswer: "19000",
      answers: [
        { buttonLabel: "19000", value: "19000" },
        { buttonLabel: "17000", value: "17000" },
        { buttonLabel: "15000", value: "15000" },
        { buttonLabel: "13000", value: "13000" },
      ],
    },
    {
      question: "What is this number?",
      phonetic: "19000",
      correctAnswer: "nineteen thousand",
      answers: [
        {
          buttonLabel: "dahanamadāha",
          value: "nineteen thousand",
          sinhala: "දහනමදාහ",
        },
        {
          buttonLabel: "dahatdāha",
          value: "seventeen thousand",
          sinhala: "දහත්දාහ",
        },
        {
          buttonLabel: "pahaḷosdāha",
          value: "fifteen thousand",
          sinhala: "පහළොස්දාහ",
        },
        {
          buttonLabel: "dahatundāha",
          value: "thirteen thousand",
          sinhala: "දහතුන්දාහ",
        },
      ],
    },
    {
      question: "What is this number?",
      phonetic: "විසිදාහ",
      correctAnswer: "20000",
      answers: [
        { buttonLabel: "20000", value: "20000" },
        { buttonLabel: "12000", value: "12000" },
        { buttonLabel: "18000", value: "18000" },
        { buttonLabel: "16000", value: "16000" },
      ],
    },
    {
      question: "What is this number?",
      phonetic: "20000",
      correctAnswer: "twenty thousand",
      answers: [
        {
          buttonLabel: "visidāha",
          value: "twenty thousand",
          sinhala: "විසිදාහ",
        },
        {
          buttonLabel: "doḷosdāha",
          value: "twelve thousand",
          sinhala: "දොළොස්දාහ",
        },
        {
          buttonLabel: "dahaaṭadāha",
          value: "eighteen thousand",
          sinhala: "දහඅටදාහ",
        },
        {
          buttonLabel: "dasayadāha",
          value: "sixteen thousand",
          sinhala: "දසයදාහ",
        },
      ],
    },
  ],
  [
    {
      question: "What is this number?",
      phonetic: "තිස්දාහ",
      correctAnswer: "30000",
      answers: [
        { buttonLabel: "30000", value: "30000" },
        { buttonLabel: "50000", value: "50000" },
        { buttonLabel: "40000", value: "40000" },
        { buttonLabel: "60000", value: "60000" },
      ],
    },
    {
      question: "What is this number?",
      phonetic: "30000",
      correctAnswer: "thirty thousand",
      answers: [
        {
          buttonLabel: "tisdāha",
          value: "thirty thousand",
          sinhala: "තිස්දාහ",
        },
        {
          buttonLabel: "panasdāha",
          value: "fifty thousand",
          sinhala: "පනස්දාහ",
        },
        {
          buttonLabel: "hatalisdāha",
          value: "forty thousand",
          sinhala: "හතලිස්දාහ",
        },
        { buttonLabel: "hæṭadāha", value: "sixty thousand", sinhala: "හැටදාහ" },
      ],
    },
    {
      question: "What is this number?",
      phonetic: "හතලිස්දාහ",
      correctAnswer: "40000",
      answers: [
        { buttonLabel: "40000", value: "40000" },
        { buttonLabel: "70000", value: "70000" },
        { buttonLabel: "50000", value: "50000" },
        { buttonLabel: "30000", value: "30000" },
      ],
    },
    {
      question: "What is this number?",
      phonetic: "40000",
      correctAnswer: "forty thousand",
      answers: [
        {
          buttonLabel: "hatalisdāha",
          value: "forty thousand",
          sinhala: "හතලිස්දාහ",
        },
        {
          buttonLabel: "hættadāha",
          value: "seventy thousand",
          sinhala: "හැත්තදාහ",
        },
        {
          buttonLabel: "panasdāha",
          value: "fifty thousand",
          sinhala: "පනස්දාහ",
        },
        {
          buttonLabel: "tisdāha",
          value: "thirty thousand",
          sinhala: "තිස්දාහ",
        },
      ],
    },
    {
      question: "What is this number?",
      phonetic: "පනස්දාහ",
      correctAnswer: "50000",
      answers: [
        { buttonLabel: "50000", value: "50000" },
        { buttonLabel: "80000", value: "80000" },
        { buttonLabel: "60000", value: "60000" },
        { buttonLabel: "70000", value: "70000" },
      ],
    },
    {
      question: "What is this number?",
      phonetic: "50000",
      correctAnswer: "fifty thousand",
      answers: [
        {
          buttonLabel: "panasdāha",
          value: "fifty thousand",
          sinhala: "පනස්දාහ",
        },
        { buttonLabel: "asūdāha", value: "eighty thousand", sinhala: "අසූදාහ" },
        { buttonLabel: "hæṭadāha", value: "sixty thousand", sinhala: "හැටදාහ" },
        {
          buttonLabel: "hættadāha",
          value: "seventy thousand",
          sinhala: "හැත්තදාහ",
        },
      ],
    },
    {
      question: "What is this number?",
      phonetic: "හැටදාහ",
      correctAnswer: "60000",
      answers: [
        { buttonLabel: "60000", value: "60000" },
        { buttonLabel: "90000", value: "90000" },
        { buttonLabel: "50000", value: "50000" },
        { buttonLabel: "30000", value: "30000" },
      ],
    },
    {
      question: "What is this number?",
      phonetic: "60000",
      correctAnswer: "sixty thousand",
      answers: [
        { buttonLabel: "hæṭadāha", value: "sixty thousand", sinhala: "හැටදාහ" },
        { buttonLabel: "anūdāha", value: "ninety thousand", sinhala: "අනූදාහ" },
        {
          buttonLabel: "panasdāha",
          value: "fifty thousand",
          sinhala: "පනස්දාහ",
        },
        {
          buttonLabel: "tisdāha",
          value: "thirty thousand",
          sinhala: "තිස්දාහ",
        },
      ],
    },
    {
      question: "What is this number?",
      phonetic: "හැත්තදාහ",
      correctAnswer: "70000",
      answers: [
        { buttonLabel: "70000", value: "70000" },
        { buttonLabel: "50000", value: "50000" },
        { buttonLabel: "90000", value: "90000" },
        { buttonLabel: "30000", value: "30000" },
      ],
    },
    {
      question: "What is this number?",
      phonetic: "70000",
      correctAnswer: "seventy thousand",
      answers: [
        {
          buttonLabel: "hættadāha",
          value: "seventy thousand",
          sinhala: "හැත්තදාහ",
        },
        {
          buttonLabel: "panasdāha",
          value: "fifty thousand",
          sinhala: "පනස්දාහ",
        },
        { buttonLabel: "anūdāha", value: "ninety thousand", sinhala: "අනූදාහ" },
        {
          buttonLabel: "tisdāha",
          value: "thirty thousand",
          sinhala: "තිස්දාහ",
        },
      ],
    },
    {
      question: "What is this number?",
      phonetic: "අසූදාහ",
      correctAnswer: "80000",
      answers: [
        { buttonLabel: "80000", value: "80000" },
        { buttonLabel: "40000", value: "40000" },
        { buttonLabel: "60000", value: "60000" },
        { buttonLabel: "90000", value: "90000" },
      ],
    },
    {
      question: "What is this number?",
      phonetic: "80000",
      correctAnswer: "eighty thousand",
      answers: [
        { buttonLabel: "asūdāha", value: "eighty thousand", sinhala: "අසූදාහ" },
        {
          buttonLabel: "hatalisdāha",
          value: "forty thousand",
          sinhala: "හතලිස්දාහ",
        },
        { buttonLabel: "hæṭadāha", value: "sixty thousand", sinhala: "හැටදාහ" },
        { buttonLabel: "anūdāha", value: "ninety thousand", sinhala: "අනූදාහ" },
      ],
    },
    {
      question: "What is this number?",
      phonetic: "අනූදාහ",
      correctAnswer: "90000",
      answers: [
        { buttonLabel: "90000", value: "90000" },
        { buttonLabel: "70000", value: "70000" },
        { buttonLabel: "50000", value: "50000" },
        { buttonLabel: "30000", value: "30000" },
      ],
    },
    {
      question: "What is this number?",
      phonetic: "90000",
      correctAnswer: "ninety thousand",
      answers: [
        { buttonLabel: "anūdāha", value: "ninety thousand", sinhala: "අනූදාහ" },
        {
          buttonLabel: "hættadāha",
          value: "seventy thousand",
          sinhala: "හැත්තදාහ",
        },
        {
          buttonLabel: "panasdāha",
          value: "fifty thousand",
          sinhala: "පනස්දාහ",
        },
        {
          buttonLabel: "tisdāha",
          value: "thirty thousand",
          sinhala: "තිස්දාහ",
        },
      ],
    },
    {
      question: "What is this number?",
      phonetic: "ලක්ෂය",
      correctAnswer: "100000",
      answers: [
        { buttonLabel: "100000", value: "100000" },
        { buttonLabel: "40000", value: "40000" },
        { buttonLabel: "60000", value: "60000" },
        { buttonLabel: "90000", value: "90000" },
      ],
    },
    {
      question: "What is this number?",
      phonetic: "100000",
      correctAnswer: "one hundred thousand",
      answers: [
        {
          buttonLabel: "lakṣaya",
          value: "one hundred thousand",
          sinhala: "ලක්ෂය",
        },
        {
          buttonLabel: "hatalisdāha",
          value: "forty thousand",
          sinhala: "හතලිස්දාහ",
        },
        { buttonLabel: "hæṭadāha", value: "sixty thousand", sinhala: "හැටදාහ" },
        { buttonLabel: "anūdāha", value: "ninety thousand", sinhala: "අනූදාහ" },
      ],
    },
    {
      question: "What is this number?",
      phonetic: "දසලක්ෂය",
      correctAnswer: "1000000",
      answers: [
        { buttonLabel: "1000000", value: "1000000" },
        { buttonLabel: "400000", value: "400000" },
        { buttonLabel: "600000", value: "600000" },
        { buttonLabel: "900000", value: "900000" },
      ],
    },
    {
      question: "What is this number?",
      phonetic: "1000000",
      correctAnswer: "one million",
      answers: [
        {
          buttonLabel: "dasalakṣaya",
          value: "one million",
          sinhala: "දසලක්ෂය",
        },
        {
          buttonLabel: "lakṣaya",
          value: "one hundred thousand",
          sinhala: "ලක්ෂය",
        },
        {
          buttonLabel: "hatalisdāha",
          value: "forty thousand",
          sinhala: "හතලිස්දාහ",
        },
        { buttonLabel: "hæṭadāha", value: "sixty thousand", sinhala: "හැටදාහ" },
      ],
    },
  ],
];
